Hello and welcome to this lesson.
I am going to show you the project.
We will be building in this course.
Now we are going to we are going to focus all of our energy on the complete authentication system.
It might look small but there is a lot that goes into building the perfect authentication system taking
care of security taking care of performance and all of that good stuff.
So first of all a user can read you stop.
So I'm going to place in my name and if I try to sign up without providing the details.
Of course we have some really clean validation I can place in my email and I can choose a password when
I sign up.
It takes a second because it sends a welcome email to the user.
Now if I check my email which is right here now we are also going to integrate e-mailing so that we
can send e-mails from anywhere in the application.
The system we are going to be setting up is scalable such that any time you can switch out for mail
trap mail gong or Amazon yes or Spock or whatever provider you actually want to use.
Now if I check the confirmation email I have a link that says please click here to confirm your account.
Now I can click on this link to confirm my account but if I visit my account I can actually see that
once my account is not confirmed I have a bar at the top that says Click here to reset e-mail.
And if I click on that link I have a confirmation that they successfully re sent email and notice the
flash messages that we have.
We are using view X to have a performance and really fast flash messaging system.
Now if I go back to my meal you can see that I have another e-mail.
Now if I click on this link it automatically tells me your e-mail has been confirmed.
Again we are using flash messages.
Now I can log out.
We have to log out functionality and we have a flash message.
Now if I click on signing and I forget my password I can go ahead and request for a password reset.
Now if I place in an e-mail that does not exist we have an error that sees this user does not exist
because we have clean error handling.
Now if I click on this we have password resettling set.
It expires in five minutes.
So we make sure that this is the correct use of request in the password reset.
So we make it expire in five minutes.
Now I'm going to copy this link instead of clicking on it and paste it here and I'm going to change
the token for the password reset.
As you can see we have a randomly secured generator token.
So if the token is invalid and I pass in a password to reset my password you can see we have an invalid
reset token.
But if I click here and now we are using the correct token and they pass in a new password and I click
on reset password we have successfully reset password flash message right there.
So this is really clean.
We also have the signing functionality where the user can pass in the email and password
we have this credentials do not match our records if the password is wrong.
And we also have cited for the use to successfully signing.
All right.
So this is what we are going to be building in a nutshell.
But the code base is gigantic because there is a lot that goes into building a real world consumer ready
application.
So in a server I'm going to teach you how to structure your application for scalability.
You can see that e-mails are stored in a specific folder.
The e-mails are in a similar text and watch a CMO for months.
You realize that we have a model folder for all of the models we have in the application and all of
our models have cleanly structured way of organizing their methods.
We also have our rules.
We have application World version for the API.
We have really clean imports right here.
We have a really good structure for the client.
Also we have components we have.
Makes sense.
We have pages.
We have the view XTO organized into modules.
We have the stars organized into a separate folder.
We have each use and help our exhaust functions create at a log goes into building this and it's going
to give you an opportunity to learn how to build a really scalable clean full stop javascript project
with Express and view Jess does a lot.
So we have the validation.
I'm going to be teaching you all of this.
So thank you for watching and see you in the next lesson.