Welcome back.
In this lesson I will show you how to get the source code for all the lessons in this course.
This is the link to the github repository is going to be available to you when you visit the github
repository.
The first thing you want to do is click on this 41 one comments right here and here you're going to
see a list of all the comments I made.
Now each committee represents a specific lesson in the cost.
So if I go to order you can see we have less than 1 initialize project and install bubble.
When you click on this comment you would see the five changes that I made in less than one and only
the five changes I made in this one.
So here we installed a new express server.
We installed the packages we need two sets of bubble.
We also created Ababa ANSI file.
You can see cleanly the changes I made.
Now let's go back and then let's go back to NEW.
And maybe we want to see the changes made in less than 40 with tweaks so you can see we installed a
flash plugin a flash Makes in we registered the mixing.
You can see we flashed messages.
We created a flash mix in right here.
We also create at a flash module for the view store and all of that good stuff.
We also installed a package to generate one dorm I.D. for flash messages.
So this is exactly how you get the source code.
Now if you want to run the project locally you just need to clone or download.
And once you do that the next step is for you to create a dot entry file.
Now dot even referrals help us keep secrets in application.
Now I want you to place a dot in the file in your projects.
So after downloading then you're going to create a dot in the file and provide the app your oh the database
your oh the mail user name and the mail password.
So this is for M. Trump to function correctly.
So you can receive mail trap that Io.
And then once you visit M. Trump you visit back coder or sorry you visit your own accounts and then
you can create a new inbox where you're going to get the mail credentials so you can see my mail credentials
like you.
So once you get those you provide exactly what we have here.
So you provide yours not mine and you provide a JWT secret for encrypting the GW cheese from the application.
You also provide your database you are often the woods me.
Now this can be for Mongo lap or you can also provide a lucario or just like I did.
Now once you do that you just need to run npm install and you are good to go.
The project is going to run successfully.
All right.
Thank you.
And see you in the next lesson.