The first step to starting a full spectroscopy project is to generate a package that Jason for NPM.
In each dash why this automatically skips all questions.
The next step is for us to install Express which is our backend server npm install safe.
EXPRESS
next year I'm going to do is create a get ignore file so that we can make sure unnecessary folders and
files are not pushed to get hot going to ignore the non modules and the puckish log.
The Jason File next I'll create a server folder where all of our server code is going to live.
Now create an indexed or just file you need which is I wrote in here going to require express
create a new express instance my calling express as a function and we can listen or create a server.
My calendar listen function.
We need to pass in the port as a first argument and the second argument is a function that will be executed
once our server has successfully started.
In this case I'm just going to log server started
to execute this far.
We can run node server slash index and you can see we have servers not that because expressed server
was successfully started at the moment.
If we make any changes to this file we would have to stop our server and started again before we see
those changes.
But we are going to install a tool code load month so we don't have to do this npm install save us a
dependency for development Node 1
now that we have no money stored no packets should use and file our create a script and this script
is going to be called
this script is going to unload on server slash index and if we want NPM 1 def you can see we have server
started now load money is going to automatically restart every time we make a change.
The next step is for us to be able to use the ESD import syntax instead of the require.
This is going to really keep our code very clean and things are clean site all so uses the ASX require
the server side should also use it for uniformity.
To do this we are going to install a couple of bubble packages and then install save.
Def the first one is going to be bubble core and this is the core bubble package.
The second one is going to be bubble slash CLIA which we are going to use to transpire that yes 6 quote
down to yes five so that we can run in production the next one is bubble slash preset EMV.
So that bubble can detect what specific version of JavaScript we are using and compile down to the correct
one last one is bubble node which is the package we are going to use along side note Hmong in development
now that those packages saying start the first thing we are going to do is modify our normal script.
I'm going to add exact bubble note and instead of using old look money is going to use my note so that
it transpires down to yes 5 before executing the code.
The next thing we're going to do is create a dot bubble.
Our CFO and inhere we are going to define a preset and the preset is going to be bubbles slash preset
Ian.
So that bubble automatically detects what version of Jaws we are using.
Now if we come to our call we can change this to import Express from Express and now let's go ahead
on one NPM one def to see if mobile is able to transfer our code and pin on Def and we have an error
that space express is not defined.
That's because we change data capital.
Great.
You can see that look monies successfully able to run could be the iOS 6 import syntax.
Now that we have both sets of we successfully sets our bubble and installed express let us continue
in the next lesson.