That's in store till when CSX reaches the CSX from what we are going to be using for this project.
If you've never used to before it's really really easy to use and you're going to have an opportunity
to learn the most amazing CSX framework on the planet.
The first thing we need to do is install a couple of dependencies.
First we'll be installing two having CSX itself but we'll also need to install post CSX which is which
will help us compare advanced CSX to what most bosses can understand.
We'll also need to install post CSX loader so he can help load that advance CSX with Westpac.
And I think that's all we need.
Next we are going to generate a tail CSX configuration file by running and p x to win in it and this
initialize the tool window.
Jess we see here next we're going to have a configuration for post CSX so CSX can feed the Jets.
And here we're going to have a module that exports and it's going to have a plugins ins and one of them
is going to be require showing CSX and will pass in showing that Jess has a config.
Now don't worry so much about CSX and all of the configurations.
What you need to know is this is a configuration for loading CSX and we need to register till we plug
it so that CSX is going to know exactly what configurations to use.
And we also have to add the post CSX loadout to our weapon configuration so that you can compare than
that advanced JavaScript we talked about.
So how are CSX loader.
Now the final step is to be able to use Tobin says sensors in our own CSX.
So in our client stars mean CSX.
When you use the towing CSX.
So we in pre-flight to lean components.
And finally till we utilities and this is different CSX packages coming from the till we package itself.
So because we have the tailwind plugging this directive is available to us and CSX knows how to handle
this company down to normal CSX.
So now that we have this if we check out the application it's to run in normally.
So if we refresh and view the beach source and view the update CSX look at that we have normal isotopes
yeses.
And this is coming from.
So when pre-flight we have a bunch of each meeting classes a lot of CSX and this is coming from the
CSX framework we just installed.
OK.
So how is this going to work to win helps us right.
Flexible CSX using utility classes.
And this is how it's going to work in the main the view we can give this element a class of text center.
This is text align center text seal which is color of teal and if I refresh.
Great.
You can see it's centralized and we have a color of teal and the awesome part about this framework is
the fact that every census we write is exactly the same way we would have written it if we were writing
this yes's directly.
So you can see text you gives it a color of 2 and text sense I guess it takes a line of center just
like we would have written it.
OK.
Don't worry you're going to know a lot about this.
Yes from what as time goes on.
Thank you so much and see you in the next lesson.