Let's sort of view Walter.
In this lesson first we're going to install it npm install safe you.
Walter
next in our clan folder we're going to have a routs the Jess file here would import Walter from view
Walter and we are going to export default.
Walter
in here we're going to make sure the mode is history so that we get rid of the hash value into your.
Oh and we're also going to define an array of what's before we define outs.
Let's come to our index Digest which is our root.
Make sure we import water from wells and past the water as an option to the new view instance.
And also we have to import water from view Walter and register it with our view for instance.
So view the use.
Walter and this is going to register a bunch of components that we can use everywhere in application
like the Walter view and Walter link.
So in our vaults we don't yet have any pages.
Let's go ahead and create a sample page.
This is going to be logging the view and another sample page register that you have a template
that says you stop.
And in this one the template is going to say logging in our main dot view.
We are going to have a DPH and this is going to act as the parents.
So in here we are going to render the Walter view component if we want to have navigation links.
We can have the water link component
and this is going to go to logging.
So we'll pass to you she calls you off logging will have one for register
now that we have to Walter links for the logging on ready stoppages will register the logging and register
us first our import logging from slash client slash pages slash logging.
And the reason why I have out here is because in my bible I'll see if I have an alias for art we probably
want to add an alias for pages so pages.
This is going to be client slash pages.
And in the rules file we can just see pages slash logging here we can register what the path is going
to be of logging on the components it's going to be logging.
One more for the registrar of register and component register bool import register form.
Pages slash register.
Now if we visit our application probably want to restart your server NPM on Def
we have an error that says can't resolve pages slash logging.
And that's because we don't view fires we actually need the extension.
So logging that view and now we're back on power successfully.
If we refresh the page we have the logging and register pages right there so we can see our water walks
correctly.
We've successfully installed our water.