Let's at Hope module replacement mental application.
The first thing we need to do is install what I call me the way.
Next we'll go to our server indexed to chess.
We're going to import this meta way
then we need to use this midway app to use my part called me to it and we'll pass in the compiler.
Now we need to figure out what definitely the way to use hot model reloading.
So we'll pass on a hot option and such a true.
Next we need to configure a weapon in the weapon file.
We're going to order new entry for Hotmail the replacement on these entries which going be wetback parts
middleware slash client where we load is equal to true.
And this is the end point to also communicate with to get the new server updates.
Finally we need to register the weapon put me to where logging and that comes from wetback.
So would require wetback and down to the plugin section will add a new wetback dot hearts module replacement
plugin.
Now let's start a server NPM one death
wetback successfully compilers reset or three thousand inspect to see if outmoded looting is activated
and there it is.
It works.
So now if we go to the mainland you can change logging to signing
we see that reflected immediately in the device in the browser.
So we have what module replacement walking now I'm going to visit the register speech and this is the
register speech.
And notice the path has changed.
It's no longer the home path buddies off slash register and now I'm going to go to the register the
view and change these to sign up bird.
We have an arrow when the boss tries to get the new update it receives an Unexpected token.
And the reason for this is because let me show you.
If we go to network
and make a change and such for the server update which is this far and look at the response you can
see that instead of receiving a javascript file we actually receive a statement.
And the reason for this or the reason why the hope module package cannot find the javascript file is
looking for it is because we haven't defined our public path correctly.
So this is what we do in our web Pachter config agree to come to output and we are going to define public
path.
And this is going to be slash referring to the past.
Right.
Yeah.
Server slash public and everything else from day on now go to indexed.
Jess I will define the public path for our web back for me the way this is going to be where parking
Feig done output dot public bus and now let's try this again.
We agreed to visit the home page visit the Red you stop and go back to register and try to change this
to register.
Give that a few seconds and we have another problem.
Everytime we refresh the beach all the other worlds apart from home do not walk correctly.
And that is because in our index that s GMO we are not correctly referencing the assets.
So our slush is gonna be fine.
We don't need to add a dot.
So if I refresh it is great.
This works called module replacement is on and if I change register to sign up we can see that sign
up automatically reflects.
Which means what module replacement walks correctly for all kinds of wows because we successfully and
perfectly configured the parts.