This is a template we are going to be following and we need to design this week to we CSX.
So let's get started now.
We are going to learn a lot about who wins SS in the process.
First let's talk about the call us if we go to the main that view and I give this a class of text to
you.
You can see that this becomes green.
Each color.
Now where is this color code to come in for and tell me the gems file.
It spots an object and in this object there is a class object and this defines all of the colors that
we are going to be using in our application.
So the team color is defined here.
We have to which is the one we are using.
And then we have different shapes of two.
So we have to light us to light and so on and so forth.
And then anytime we have the text we can attach the name of the color that we want to give to this element.
So we have text you we can have text read since we have the red color defined in our til we see SS config.
We can have text blue if we want.
In this case for our design we have a brown each color.
We have a good each color and for the buttons if we check out the other designs we have a greenish color.
So this is going to be available to you.
I'm just going to go to my two weeks yeses and paste these colors.
So we have em out which is the greenish color.
We have gold which is the gold color and Brown which is the brownish color.
So now we can use these custom colors in our application.
So for example we can see text gold and you can see we have that good color right there.
So now that we have our own custom color palette and the where you can actually get these.
OK so you can check the source code for this lesson and you just copy this palette that I pasted.
I prepared it beforehand.
Next thing we're going to take care of is the funds so funds that could come and we want to search for
merry weather.
So this is the funds when you add the funds customize it add a bold and other light and I'll copy the
import coming to my main dot CSX and paste the import there.
So now that I have the Merriweather forms I can come to my towing CSX and configure these funds.
So if you search for funds in this configuration file you can see that we have funds and then we have
the name of the funds and then the order in which this form sheet should be loaded so we can add our
own funds if we want.
We have signs we have Sunseri We have money.
Let's add our own.
This is going to be primary and this is going to be Merriweather at the top which means everyone wants
to buy my font.
We are going to give it a colossal font primary.
So let's try that funds primary and if I call now you can see that this has a font of primary which
is r Merryweather fonts.
So let's just make sure that all elements on the page have this font so goods our index that estimable
and add this to the body class of funds primary.
OK.
That works.
We have the font configured.
Let's start taking care of our layout.
Looks like we need a top bar with this gold ish color in our main that view.
I'm going to add a DPH with a class of etch to an edge to ease us.
She has a slide that takes care of the height.
So if you come through a chill wind at CSX and such for height you find out the high comments and you
can see we can have edge with the size of the height and edge too in this case is zero point five Ram.
So it's just like wait and see SS but it's pretty quick.
So now I have a class of etch 2.
I'm gonna give this a with of four which is a width of one hundred percent.
And again you can check out the till we say SS 5 4 with and you'd see we have we've of auto p x 1 and
the one I'm using right now is for y down here which is 100 percent.
So with W full which means means with 100 percent.
And then I'm just gonna say be off good.
And this means background color of good and you can see we have the go top border right there.
And I think this should be called light because it looks a little lighter.
OK.
So just like that.
That's our top model without waiting any line of CSX.
Really flexible.
Next we have this section that has the logo and the two buttons.
So we probably want to have a bar of four with a bit of padding on the edges.
So what we're going to do is have a diff class is going to be off with form.
The height is going to be of twelve we can check height to see what twelve is and two of his three room.
So we can play around with those values to make sure we have the correct one edge of twelve.
Let's just give this a border so that we can see what we are dealing with.
So butter gives us a bottle of one piece so solid and what I read gives is color of red.
So that's the border there.
So we can see the dimensions we are dealing with now to be able to control the items in this container.
I'll give this a display of flex and items center which means a line item center and justified content
center to just weigh the content center.
Then I'm going to have a def for the logo for.
So for start Jess in this case I'll just call it man.
MELVIN OK.
Because it's the Melvin stock and you can see it's justified center but we don't want to just fight
sent out what we want we actually just fight between so that we're going to have two days or two children
and they're going to be floated to each end of the Flex container.
So I'm going to add another child and in here we're going to have a navigation links.
So I'll just cut out the Walton links that we have here and it here and great.
So you can see we have a fiber content between walking perfectly.
We have never.
And then we have the logging register.
It looks like this container actually has a very large putty just like in the styling here.
So let's add that buddy.
So let's give this a padding ex of twelve and maybe 12 is a lot.
Let's try six and six looks great.
So putting X which means horizontal padding of six.
Now it looks like the color of the logo should actually be good.
So we are going to say text gold and great.
Now the color of the logging unregistered buttons are actually brown.
So we are going to make sure this is text brown and gray.
That looks fine.
I would give the same class to the register and we also do not want it to be underlined.
So we'll give this a class of no on the line.
Make sure we give this the same class.
And we probably want to change this to sign in and change these to join now just like it is in our template.
Now the register button actually has a border.
So let's give this a border and we we're also going to give this a border broad so that the border isn't
Brown.
Just like in the template but the border here looks so thin and in the template it looks thicker.
So we'll give this a mother of two and I think that's good.
Now it also has a potty.
So we're going to see p. five and that's a little too much.
So let's try P. of two and I think that's a K. maybe try P. of one and I think that's perfect.
So now that we have the putting the next thing is to make it round so we're going to see round it and
this guess is of small but outrageous.
We're going to give it one that fool for a complete butter reduce and I think that's great.
Now let's get rid of the body red since we had done in the element and now we need to give a little
space between the joint now and the signing.
So we are going to come to the signing of the joint now and give this a margin left of three and great.
That's the speech we need it.
Finally we need to make sure the text right here for start Jess Mearns Stata is centralized so we have
to actually come to the home page which is here and make sure we add that text we don't yet have a home
component.
So let's create one.
So at home the view and in the wilds I'm going to import home
from Page's home that view and add that Welch
and in the home we define our template on Def OK.
So the home looks good.
Now let's give this an etch one of Texas Center.
So X on the text center the text Brown.
And this is going to see an easy end.
Great.
But now we also need some spacing from the top.
So let's give this a glass of margin y 32 and this is of margin top and bottom of 32 units.
So if you want to make sure or know what to do two stands for you can concerto in such for margin and
then check out the 32 value you can see that that's 8 REM.
Okay.
So that's it using Tobin's yeses.
It's a really really easy process to design exactly what we need.
So thank you so much.
And then the next lesson will continue having fun with these projects.