We'll be designing this queen in this lesson.
But before we do that let's do some more work on this button.
I'm going to introduce a couple of things to you so first instead of giving this a P. one I'm going
to give this a p x three and a P Y off to definitely looks better than what I want is when they use
a whole vase over this button.
You should actually have a darker brown so the way you define effects with the win is 2 1/2 over a on
and then the stars that you want to be applied when they use a Hoovers for example.
Text Brown darkest should be the text.
So if I Hoover you can see that the text changes so I can also change the border.
So Hoover butter brown darkest and if I Hoover now you can see the whole thing changes.
Let's also make sure the logo is a link so I'm just going to change these two on a.
Or actually a Walton link so that it navigates recline side while chin and chew is going to be the homepage
and we'll say no on the line so that it's not decorated and it works.
Now let's go to the register peach in the register view.
First we're going to have a container on the container.
Basically restricts the width of contents.
So if I give a body to this container on the height so I'm just going to say with full so that it has
a full with then at 12:00.
And by brown red you can see that the container on the screen fills the whole screen.
But if I increase a screen you can see that the container just feels a part of the screen.
OK now I'm going to give this container an M X auto for my Jean Auto.
So that it's centralized and you can see on this screen is centralized.
But on smaller screens it fills the whole screen.
OK.
So that's a really good responsive container.
Next we're going to have this cart that we see.
So we're going to have this section and that is in the container so I'll quit a leave Max with small.
And this gives the diff a max width and you can check.
So when she says to see
what small represents that's 30 REM.
So Max with of 30 m m ex auto background white etched twelve so if I expand this you can see this is
it covering this area of the container.
So we are just using height and color right now to play with this.
Let me just give these background green so we can see better.
So you can see the background green there.
So that's our max with small probably want to try Max with extra small that's smaller.
So I think we're going to go with this.
So in this container we are going to have an each one the text center.
And this is going to see register OK.
And remember the color has to be gold based on our makeup and I think that sex is to be competitive
makeup.
So maybe we want to reduce this to edge for Yeah that's too small.
Let's try and edge too.
And if it's too big we're going to UCSF to reduce it.
So she thinks it's too big.
We're going to give this a text of large and I think that's perfect.
So we can also give this container a margin why of 16 so that it is a little far away from the top.
Now let me remove the colors and the heights.
We do need that.
I mean more and the next thing we need to do is add our quite card.
So after the head you're going to have a container of with for that background.
Right.
And let's just give this a choice so we can design it maybe change by quality green.
Yeah.
So that's our day.
So the problem is the background blends with the background of the peach.
So the diagram of the peach is actually not supposed to be white.
Right.
So that the background white of this element actually shows up and the background of the peach.
I'm going to define it in I mean that CSX.
So I already have defined.
You're just going to have it available.
So I'm just gonna see body and background.
Is this really light cream color right here.
So F E F the FAA.
So now if we come back to the register and make this background of white and give this a shadow large
great you can see the background of white is a little visible.
So maybe this should just be a shadow.
And that's good enough.
So I don't know if you can notice but a background for the body is a little different because of the
styling be added.
OK.
So now let's give this a margin top of five just so that it's a little way from the head.
And let's give this a round that class just so that it has a little nice buttery juice and the battery
juice looks a bit too much for me.
So I'm going to reduce that you assume.
Great.
So round that.
Awesome.
Ok so now in our cart we are going to have inputs.
OK.
So this is our input.
Let's give it a couple of classes with full force starts us and you can see that's our input right there.
And if we want the contents of the car to be restricted we can give it a padding so we can say p. 6
and if we check the input now it's centralized somehow but because of the height we put it's messed
up.
Let's move the height and now you can see it's perfectly centralized.
We probably want to give this p off because this like a lot of putting from the template.
Yes.
Now we are going to have some more styling for the input.
We're going to give this a background of Brown the lightest and that's the color of the input box in
our template.
Then we want to give this a putty so that the input is really large.
So p y 0 5.
And that's a little much.
Let's try three.
And I think that's perfect.
BURT We don't want this this blue border our input so we're going to see for.
So that's the focus date outline should be known.
And if I click on that you can see the outline is no bird.
We also don't want the text in the input tree luck.
We actually want it to be brown.
So why wouldn't you say text Brown and we also want who is zones are putting in the input like that.
So we probably won't actually use P 3.
So that each horizontal and vertical like that.
And then I think the text in the input such really really large.
So we probably want to use text small maybe try to text extra small.
Yeah.
And I think that's perfect.
Okay guys.
So now let's out of place holder to see if it actually looks like a template.
So enter your name.
Great.
So that's our name.
So you can see how easy it is to actually design this thing with tail win.
We are just actually writing CSX.
Yes.
So now let's duplicate the input for email and password so I'll duplicate this
into your email and enter your password.
Burt we also need a matching bottom so that they are spaced out so Margene bottom of five margin bottom
of five.
Great.
That's the speech we need maybe a little too much on the padding.
So I'm just gonna give this a party of eight and the margin shouldn't be that much modern.
Bottom of three should be enough.
And finally let's at the bottom.
So here I'm gonna have a button and let's give this a couple of classes with four so that it spans the
whole container.
And this is going to see sign up and let's give it a margin.
So Margene top off three so that it speaks and then let's give it a putting y of four and let's give
this a background of Emerald which is the name of a really nice blue color.
So why don't we give this budding white or three and it actually should be the same pattern with the
input boxes.
Right.
And then let's give this a text of white and let's give these around that small so that it's a little
rounded but not so obvious.
And let's remove the outline for a course outline known.
So if I click on that there's no outline.
And let's give this over states.
So whoever background should be Emerald lighter.
And if I refresh try to Hoover you can see it's light.
But we should actually use light instead of lighter.
Great.
So the text in the bottom looks really large.
So I probably wanna do text small and I think it's too large because of my enlargement but anyway.
That's fine.
OK.
So that's our design.
We have our richest touch screen completely design and just like that.
OK.
So I think that design is ready we can go ahead and use this.