Let's create a custom impute component so that we can reuse components across different pages.
First thing we're going to do is create a components folder here.
I'm going to create text input.
That view sees this as a component that will be used by most pages which are the index that jazz import
text input
and register it as a global view component here.
The component text input text input.
Why do we have an alias for the components folder.
So I'll add one component
points to the client slash components folder the next step is to extract her input from the register
since that's where we designed it and actually put it in the text input.
So I'll take the input copy one of them and place it there.
We'll accept some props.
So our defined script.
Export default an object
would accept a place holder of type String required.
True we'll also accept a type of type String required of falls and defaults to text.
Now how do we use the text input in the register component instead of having this input.
We can have text compute
and pass into props we need for example the place holder is going to be and SA you name where we need
to bind the value of the prop in the component.
So instead of having enter your name here we are going to bind it to place holder which is an incoming
crop and now in our register if we change these two names we can see it reflected in the register.
I'll do final scripts
and I'll define the dates for these components
I would have a model and here would have a name would also have an email and would also have a password.
And this actually represents the data that we are going to be collecting for my user.
So I would say the model is a quality model that name and if I open up my view death dos search for
the register component and check out the model sites I realize that it doesn't show up automatically
because this is a custom regex component for each walk we need to pass down the value which is going
to be model that name into this component and we're going to receive the value prop of type String required
false and defaults to an empty string and we are going to mind it to the input
so we are successfully binding the value but now we need to meet on events every time this input in
this component changes so we are going to see that image is going to be quality image to impeach events
with event that I get not value.
And now if we check out the register component monitor each model as we change the name you can see
the name automatically reflected.
Now let's do the same thing for the email and the password
and we can eliminate the other two inboxes we have.
So if we check register component and I type the name populates type the email it populates the type
the password it populates which means we have a successful custom VHS component.