Let's add validation to the register form to do that.
We are going to npm install the validate.
And this is a package that's going to help us validate our forms really easily.
Next we need to register this form with our view instance.
So in the index suggests for the client would import value data from V validate and we would use this
review.
And now if we check out our component give this a refresh and view the register component specifically.
You can see we have new computer properties for errors that the feuds object is empty which is supposed
to represent all the future we have in our form.
And the reason why it's empty is because we need to define the name for each of the future we have in
our form.
So we are going to pass a name pop to the input component we created.
So the name of this is going to be name.
The e-mail is going to be email and the password is going to be password.
And finally we need to go to the text input and make sure we receive this pop.
The name is going to be of type String and is required.
And we need to bind that name today input.
Now we need to define the validations for each of these fields.
We are going to pass a v validate attribute and this is going to be a string containing the violation
rules for the name.
It's only going to be required for the e-mail.
It's going to be required and type e-mail.
And finally for the password it's going to be required and a minimum of six characters.
Now if we come back to our application I give this a refresh visit the register component and check
out the future.
You can see we have the email name and password fields.
And each of these has these are containing if there are changed dirty involved pending as we type in
this input fields we can see validation rules populated in the items are we.
So the e-mail must be a valid email.
And as we type in the password we have the was showing up the form doesn't work properly yet because
the events that we need to admit from the input so that we validate is going to know when to properly.
An example of these events is the focus so that we value did not show end of input has been focused
and we just image focus so that we knew when the form has been touched or the form input has been touched
would also emit blur to know when the user has blurred out of this input.
And this is going to be blurred we also meet change and this is going to happen when they use user changes
the value of this input and it's going to emit the same value as the input.
Now if we visit our form and give this a good refresh
as we type our name.
If I delete the value
we have the name how US populate it when this form is submitted.
What we want to do is make sure the data in the form is validated before actually making an API request
to register the user to do that in the register that view when this button is clicked we'll call or
register method
and will define our methods.
And here we can call this that validate or validate to validate all of the data.
And this returns a promise with are is valid value and this value tells us if the form is valid.
So if it's valid then we are going to proceed.
But if it's not valid.
Now we are going to return early so that the user does not get to submit the form.
So now if we check out our form visit the register component you can see the items are easier when I
click on that.
The items are is three because I try to submit the form and the value data or how to validate the data
now.
We need to display the arrows for these input fields so we are going to be passing an error prop to
each of them.
So this is going to be errors that first
password will do the same for email and the same for name in the text impute we have when you receive
the error probe as a string
and required is false.
Then we can display the error in this component.
What we are going to do is create a D
and put the input in it and I'm going to move the magic bottom to this diff and remove it from the input
so that it doesn't push the hour down and I'm going to have a span of text read for the error.
So here I'll just play the error and not only make sure this is displayed.
If there is an error.
Now if I visit the form you can sign up you can see the errors.
Sure.
But if I want these hours to be smaller I can give these a text of extra small
and now I think of the perfect size.
So as we type we can see the validation rules show up perfectly.
And once the violation rules are cleared we have the data correctly formatted.
And now if we submit a form everything should go well.
So that's how we can include validation really easy with the validated package.