We are going to install view X in application in this lesson.
Npm install safe view x next will create a store folder in our clients and this is going to have an
index to yes in this file.
We'll create a new view X instance.
First would import view X and we'd also import view so we can register each view.
Then we would use view X with view.
Then we can export default New View X that store and for our store we are going to be having different
modules so that we can easily structure our data.
The first module we are going to be having is the off module for everything that has to do with authentication.
This module is going to have an index suggests for the state mutations that just for mutations actions
digest for actions and gets us but Jess forgets us in the index largesse would import each of these
flowers so import mutations for mutations gets us
actions and we are going to export the default and objects.
This object is going to have a state for an empty object at the moment he's going to have actions gets
us and mutations in each of these files we are going to export an object by default
and now in our main index digests we can import this module import off from off and use them in our
application so we'll define a modules object and add of in it.
So now we have our module.
If we visit application we open our def 2s this exude def Touche we still have no view extort detected.
The final step of the installation process is to use the store with our view X instance.
So here we're going to import store from store and past the store to our new instance and if we visit
obligation on refresh we can see that we have a reduced store.
If we load the state all we have is an off empty object.
The first action we are going to be having is to register a user.
So we are going to export a constant export constant Post Register and this is going to be a call to
post register.
This constant is going to make sure we don't have typos when we reuse this string.
We are going to have an action for Post Register and this is going to make an asynchronous call to the
server to register a user.
Now for us to make asynchronous calls we are going to be requiring exists.
So I mean store eggs year
and now that we have existing stores I'm going to create a new folder called details and in here I'll
have an excuse.
Jess so that we can create a reusable excuse instance.
And here I'll import X years from X years and I'm going to export default x years that creates and for
the only configuration we need based you are.
So that here we can see the you are only slash API slash version 1 and we can add a slash at the end.
So this is very important so that when your client side begins to use version 2 of your API you just
need to bump this up to version 2 and in the whole project we don't need to rewrite this path because
it's already defined in our existing instance now in our actions we can import the existing instance
we created.
So import clients we can call it clients from our clients slash each those slash exerts.
And here we can have an our function that returns clients that post to the auth slash register end point
and it's going to pass data.
The first argument into any action is the context and the second argument is data that we can pass from
where this action is called.
So the second argument to our client that boost is going to be data.
We've defined an action called Post Register.
We can actually trigger this action in the register component or the register speech when the user clicks
on the register.
So let's import that action here.
Import boost register from store slash off slash actions because that's where it was exported from.
And when the user successfully passes validation we can call this dot store the dispatch that action
and we'll pass in this dot model as the detail we want to send to that action.
Then the action receives the data here and calls client dot post which is making a post request to our
server to these specific endpoints with the data that was passed.
So now let's try this out to see if it works or we haven't ever that same kind of resolve.
Clients each use excuse let's make sure the directory folder is correct and let's see Babu aliases.
We don't have an alias for clients so let's create that.
So we'll have our clients.
And this is going to be slash clients and why we're here.
Let's add an alias for the store.
So we'd have store.
And this will point to client slash store and and we have an error about a syntax.
I think for this we need to restart our server.
So just restart my server
and everything was fine refreshing and ready to go.
Now if I click on sign up failed validation rules that if I provide my details
and click on sign up we can see it makes an API request our server gives us 0 4 0 4 which is a good
thing.
It means that our action is successfully dispatched it successfully makes the API request to express
server in the next lesson we are going to begin handling this server side of things.