For the registration process we need to define I use our model in the server folder.
I'll quit on models folder on here.
I'll have a use other Jess first.
All important on this.
Next I'll create a user's came.
And this is going to be a new Mongoose that schema will pass an object and configuration for ask chemo.
We agreed to have a name and email a creator that to know when to use our age instead of data that in
case the user updates a feud like resetting the password.
We're going to have a password.
We're going to have email confirmed that to know when the user confirmed their email an email confirmed
code to have an activation code for the user's email.
Next we are going to export default a model so export Mongoose that model and the model is going to
be called user and this camera is going to be user US Kimo.
The next step is to handle creation of the user in our Controller.
Oh and by the way in the last lesson when we made an API request to the server we had a photo for let
me show you.
If I fill in the form
and click we have a 4 0 4 and the server sees this world does not exist.
But this world actually exits and the problem is in our auth all the vaults must always start with a
slash.
So here we also have to make sure it starts with a slash all express worlds have to start with a slash.
And now if we try to submit again he doesn't tell us for or for anymore it's just pending because we
are not handling this action yet.
So in our controller we need to handle the action and to undo that we need to bring in I use our model.
So our import user form models slash user and let's make sure the models alias exist it doesn't.
So we've added models is going to point to serve our slash models.
Here we need to register a new user and the cleanest way to do this is to actually make this and a sync
function so that we can always use other create and will pass in the details for this user.
First we'll get the name email and password from the body so we'd get name email password and this is
going to be the data from the client site then we are going to pass this
to the newly created user.
This promise returns towards the newly created user.
And we can return response with a status of 2 or 1 with adjacent that contains the newly created user.
At the moment we can't actually have access to request the body because our data is not yet passed to
be able to pass the detail we are going to install the body parts are middleware that helps us do this
automatically lets Reggie studies me the way we express in our index the Jess file so I'm going to import
body parser
and after reaching my express instance I'm going to use it update use body parser
by Jason and let's make sure our server is running it looks like it crashed so we are going to restart
it
and once that's restarted let's try to register a new user.
Again and we have a 2 0 1 created.
And if you check out the preview you can see this is the details of the newly registered user.
This works fine but there is two pieces of data that we are missing.
The first one is the fact that the password is not being hashed and this is a security failure.
And the second one is the fact that we don't yet set the email confront code for the user so they use
ice not yet able to confirm their email.
We also do not yet set the created app for the user and we are going to do all of these in the next
lesson.