Too harsh to use as password to the database before saving.
We are going to install a library card be equipped jests and to generate a random e-mail confront code.
We are going to install a package called random string
now in I use our schema we can define a pre safe hook which is executed before saving a new instance
or a new documents.
The database users can model pretty safe to pass a function.
And here we can say this that password which is referring to the newly created user.
And we need to hash the common user's password or the current password for the user unsafe to the database.
To do that our import B script from the secret package we installed on this that password which is the
common use us plain password is going to be equal to the hash version and we are going to hash this
synchronous.
And will pass in the current password so the password of the user will not be equal to the hashed version
of the plain password.
We also need to set the confirmation code so this not email confirmed code is going to be close to a
string.
But we want this to be random and very secure.
So we are going to import random string from the random string package we installed.
And this is going to be random string generate and we pass in the number of characters.
In this case let's use 72.
So before saving a user he is going to have to use US password and said the email confirm code what
we can do is also set the creator up.
And this is going to be new dates so that we know when this use of registered their accounts.
Now let's try to register another new user and see the data we get from the API response.
If I click on sign up and if we open the response you can see that we have the correct user's data.
The email confirmed code was generated the creator that is saved and the password is hashed and secure.