In this lesson let us set up a database connection.
The first thing we're going to do is install our package which we are going to use to connect to our
database which is Mongoose
once that's done installing in our index suggests why we can import Mongoose
and using Mongoose we can create a database connection language that connect and what Mongoose expects
to receive is the database connections train and you need to have Mongo to be running locally.
This is a sample string for your development environment right now.
If we launch our application with no crashes it means that Mongoose was able to connect to a database
lets one young Dev or NPM on Dev to check this out.
And we have servers that that successfully we need to use the new parser to get rid of that warning.
So I'm going to pass in use near you are all parts are true and you can see that that one in is normal
in different environments like in production it becomes very insecure to expose your database connection
string like this.
So the skill we are the most secure way to deal with this is to use environment variables.
For this we are going to be using a package called EMV.
This is going to give us the possibility of defining all of our involvement variables in an environment
file and depending on the environment where we are.
These credentials are going to change at the roots of my projects.
I'm going to quit the EMV file here.
I'm going to define database your URL and I'm going to move what I have here into the that and we file
the next one I'm going to do some winter import dot in the
from the India and I need to call the EMV the config so that the envy the package is going to read all
of the values from the EMV file and it's going to populate process not envy in the application.
So once that package is ready we can one process that EMV dot database on that score.
You are and this is automatically going to be the you are all of our database to make sure everything
is still fine because one NPM one def to see if it starts successfully and it successfully starts it
becomes a little difficult to manage your application when the environment tables are accessed directly
from process that in the what we are going to do is we are going to create a config for the can here.
I'm going to have an index or just file.
This is going to export an object and all of our conjugations are going to be here which assess the
process.
Ian Lee for example our database your eye is going to be processed in the database your AI or.
Then I'm going to pass in a default.
I will just get the one for my involvement and this is a truly data issue.
Oh now in my server I can get rid of this dog in V and actually put it in my configuration file so that
in the config is going to be initialized in my congregation file since that's where we are defining
AI investment vehicles.
Now in my server I can import config from config and replace this week config the database you are this
way.
Even if a user does not define a database you are in the involvement label.
The config is automatically going to use the default which we've defined right here.
And this is a more reasonable approach to have for your applications now to make sure everything is
running correctly.
We want NPM on death and everything so start successfully.
Which means our application is fine.