For a user to be able to confirm their accounts we need to send him an email containing that email confirm
quote when they click on this link it automatically confirms their account.
The first thing we're going to do is install the package we are going to use to send emails called First
digest mail once this package is installed.
We can run MP X friend Lee mail in it.
And this is going to generate a configuration file at the root of application.
So this configuration file can help us configure the credentials useful sending emails.
First we can find a connection by default.
It's 70 B.
We can define the folder where all of our e-mails will be saved and by default.
It's just a Mills folder.
But what we want to do is actually save them in server slash mills so that the mills are on the server.
Then we have view engine.
In this case we are just going to default to handlebars and we can now define the credentials for a
70 B connection.
So it looks like we need an SMG port and SMG host a username and password.
Now you can use any service issue like you can use Park post you can use mill going you can use SS with
this package but in this case since we're in testing we are going to use mail truck.
And if you don't have a military account make sure you get one it's free.
This can help you send in those in development.
So this is my mail Trump account.
And when you log into your military account I'll just delete this inbox so I show you from scratch.
You can create a new inbox and pass in a name.
So I'll call this Melvin which is the name of our course.
And when I visit the inbox you can see credentials for that inbox present that you meet.
So notice the host is here.
The ports are here that we can use and the user name is provided also.
So we have to define these in our environment file so in the end the mail user name is going to be equal
to the value we copied form mail drop and we also have to define the mail password configuration so
I'll copy that from mail Trump.
Also
now remember we are not defining the host on port because these are already the defaults now that we
have that the next thing is for us to generate a mail so we can see n x friendly mail generate and the
name of these mail is going to be confirm accounts and it saves the mail has been generated successfully.
If we check in our server mails folder which is a form that we specified for our mails we have three
templates generated.
We have control account of HMO for still more parts of our mail than for text and then in case you want
to send for the Apple Watch You can also define how the email should look here.
Now in the confirmed HMO we are going to see hey I will pass in the name of the user who is trying to
activate the account so we can make this strong since this is HMO and we can have a break so that it
goes on the next line and we can say Please confirm your accounts by clicking on this your hour.
And we are going to pass in.
There you are.
But since this is HMO we can have an edge with and possibly you are right here now for text.
I'm going to copy this and pasted in text when it's text.
We can't have the strong tax so we're just going to have name.
We can't have the break and we can't have the ref.
So we're just going to have the link like that.
But what's important is that we make sure we pass the name under you all.
So how do we send an e-mail.
We are going to come to use our model and this is the pre safe for when they use ace about to be saved
through the database we have when you use a post safe when the user is already safe.
To the database.
So when they use a successfully registered we are going to send an e-mail to that user.
And how do we send an e-mail using this package.
We are going to import mail from full digest slash mail and all we need to do is return New Mail and
the name of the mail is confirm accounts and we have to define who we are sending that mail to this
is going to be this that e-mail and we can possibly use us names so that it's available in the mail
so we can see this dot name and we can set a subject for this e-mail which is going to please confirm
your account and we can send data to the template that we defined for the mail and in the template is
expecting a name which is going to be d dot name.
And it's also expecting a U R O which is an activation you are out for the user to click on and this
activation you O has to contain the e-mail confirmed.
OK.
So this is what we are going to do.
We are going to say this dot e-mail confirm called but it has to be off slash e-mails slash confirm.
Then the e-mail confirm code.
But we also have to make sure that we have the correct you are all for the application so that when
the user clicks it brings the user back to the application at the moment.
We are using look our host for three thousand but to make sure that if this value changes in the production
environment we are still going to be fine.
Would you find this in our config.
So here we are exporting database you.
We are going to export you now which is going to be processed that EMV not app on this call you are
0 or the default which is esta to be local host three thousand.
Now in our environment file we can define app your all
and this is going to be local hotspot three thousand.
So in I use our model to make sure our code is stable and does not change in future.
We're going to import config from config and let's make sure we have the config alias in our bubble
our c file yes we do.
OK.
So to send the mail we are also going to concatenate config that you are Oh right here.
So config that you are slash of e-mails confirm and then the e-mail confirm code.
And finally we are going to call it a send method to send the mail.
So after the user account is saved we are going to send the e-mail using this and this send method actually
returns a promise so we can make this sink and then use our weight here so that the user actually sees
the successful response only after the e-mail is sent.
Now let's try this out.
We need to come to our browser revisit the application and try to register a new user UN member we are
using M. trap which is going to trap the e mails.
It's not going to send any real e-mails so let's pass in the password for the user and click on sign
up and we can see that it takes a moment to complete the API request.
And now we have to 0 1 create it.
And if we check mail drop like that we have an e-mail sent since we defined to we have the name of the
user.
And we also have the e-mail of the user.
Then if we check out our esta M.O. We have Hey Dr. Strange please confirm your accounts by clicking
on this.
Oh and if we copy this you are oh you can see the confirmation code here is exactly the confirmation
code we have for this user so when the user clicks on this link he takes it a user to our client site
of the application and the user account is activated but we don't yet have these functionality set up.
We are going to set this up in adolescence.