Registering a user takes about three to four seconds because we are trying to send an e-mail for confirming
the account.
We are going to add a loading State of the button so that why the user waits for the email to be sent
they can see a loading button to do this.
I've included unloading the PNC file into our public folder and you can have access to this.
When I overload the code to get.
We have to configure our server to be able to serve this static file so in the index suggests right
before we configure our gets wired card we are going to use the Express static middleware
and this is going to resolve the path for the current directory name and he's going to serve from the
public folder and make sure this Middleware is defined after the Web def middleware so often defining
this when the client side requires the loading the PMG.
It's going to be solved from this public folder so sets up our loader we are going to have a Luda component
and this is simply going to be an image with source loading the PSG.
Next we're going to have a button component and this is going to be of the same template as the button
we have in our register.
So I'll cut this out and paste it in the button component to use these globally.
We are going to come to our index the for our clients and import these two components.
Then we'll register them with view that component
the name of the loader is loader and of the button Beattie B10.
So in our register we can mount the component using BGF.
We need to define a couple of props that is Watson is going to receive.
First it's going to receive a disabled prop and this is going to be disabled.
It's also going to emit the Click event when clicked.
Let's define the props.
The first is going to be just a mode of type boolean.
It's not required and the default is false.
Next we'll have a label prop of type String and it's required
next we'll have a loading prop
of type boolean.
It's not required and the default is false.
How do we use the looting prop we are going to display a loader if this button is loading.
So V if loading will display a load up and would simply have a spine displaying the label if the button
is not loading.
We are also going to change the classes when the button is loading.
So instead of giving this a background of Emerald we are going to have a dynamic class who pass an object
and background of M0 out is going to be used when the component is not looting and background of Emerald.
Light is going to be used when the component is loading.
So we also want to give this a class of cars not allowed so that the castle is disabled on this button
when looting.
Now in our distorted view let's fast approach required will pass in a label.
This is going to be sign up will pass in disabled and we don't yet have this configured.
We need to be able to control when the component is looting and when it's not.
So in our data would have a looting this would default to.
We are going to have a method called toggle loading
and you squint you said this that loading to be a coach.
Not this not loading and disabled is going to be bound to loading.
So when the video starts loading the button disabled Pop is going to be true then would also bind loading
to be equality loading and I think that's all the props we need for the button now.
Finally when the user clicks on the button it should still call the register method.
So I click as you call to register and also when the register method is called We want to make sure
we toggle loading and when the richest start is done we want to also make sure we toggle loading and
we can also redirect the user.
At this point if we want my seeing this Walter the push and we can redirect the user to the homepage.
The reason why we can use that then is because our action returns a promise because launches that we
simply return play on the post which returns a promise.
So now I saw where it started.
Let's check this out in the browser
if we watch our network
pass in a name email and password.
Click on sign up.
Notice that the loader is displayed and once the API request is done it redirects the use of back to
the homepage.
What an improvement we need to make to our leader is the fact that the image does not speak so we are
going to go to our leader component.
Give this a class of Luda and in our main dot CSX we can define this class
so this class has an animation duration of two thousand milliseconds an animation name of spin and all
these dots is transforms it from zero to 20 and 60 degrees indefinitely.
So let's try this out.
We'll type in a fake name email and password and you can see that I love the spins.
And when the registration is successful the user is redirected back to the homepage.