When they use ice when you start the only thing we return is they use US data.
We also want to do is return on authentication token using JWT.
This is going to be used to authenticate the user when making for their request.
The first thing we need to do is install the Jason Webb tokens package
next in use our model.
We are going to import this package
and define an instance method on the user's schema so that we can use this method to generate a token
methods that generate token he's going to be a cultural function.
This function returns JWT that sign and will pass in the data we want to sign.
In this case we are just passing in the I.D. of the user.
And we also need to pass in on a secret and this secret is going to be the secret used to sign the token
in our investment vehicle.
Let's define a new vehicle code secret.
And this has to be a randomly generated string so you can even use a BCG if you want.
But the more random the string the more secure it is.
So in our config we are going to export a new config code JWT secret
and this is going to be process.
The EMV not JWT secret or one two three four
then we are going to pass config the JWT secret to this function.
So this method where we call it is going to generate a random token or adjacent web token for this user
and return to us.
So in our controller after registering a user we are going to create a token.
And this is going to be equal to user to generate token and the token is going to be part of the response
sent to the browser.
Now let's try to register a user in the browser.
I'll click and join now
watch our network pass in a fig user's dittos
and click on sign up it's loading and once it's done.
If you check out the response we now have a token which is a valid JWT for this user.
This is what is going to be used to authenticate the user father.
That's all I have for this lesson.
BIRD That's a little bug I want to fix before I close the lesson which is in the register form.
We have to make sure we pass type of password to this field but it's not working.
So in the text input we have to bind type 2 be the type prop that was passed in so that the password
field is hidden.
So if I come back to my joint now you can see that the password field is now hidden.