Let's persist authentication state to local storage so that when the user refreshes the beach the user
is still locked in.
The first thing we are going to do is in our actions we are going to export a new constants on it's
called set off on this constant is going to be used to set authentication into mutations.
I'm going to import this constant
and defined the mutation for it.
First the mutation takes in state and he's going to taking a payload with the user on token.
And this is going to define state the user to vehicle to user and state that token to be equal to the
token.
Now we need to commit this mutation once the user successfully registers a new account.
So we'll go to the register that you import this constant code set off and after successful registration
before we do it in the user we are going to commit this mutation.
So this not store the comet set off and the payload we need to send to the comet is from the response
which we receive here and we are going to send response dot data which is the data returned from the
API call.
Now we also need to process this to local storage.
So we are going to call low cost of each dot set item and the name of this item is going to be off and
the value is going to be the string defined version of responsible data.
Now let's try this out.
I'm going to open on my dev tools and I'm going to open on my view.
Doors open on my view stop and let's watch the mutations.
I'm going to register an account.
Click on sign up.
We are redirected to the home page.
As you can see a new mutation code set off is committed.
And if we load the stage you can see that our state has a token and user objects form the API response.
And if we check out our application look our store which you can see we have the user key there which
is our data from the API.
But if I refresh my page local store which is persistence.
But the view store has been cleared and if we load the state now the author is still an empty object.
What we want to do is make sure that the default value or the default state of our view store is gotten
from local storage.
To do that we are going to come to our index suggests and we are going to define initial state records
nor then in a try catch block we are going to try to decode the data from local storage.
So we are going to say initial stage is equal to Jason the pass Look out storage.
That gets item off and if there is any ever when trying to decode these data for example the data has
been tampered with or there is no data at all then we are going to set initials dates to equal to an
empty object that has user of lower and token of law.
And we are going to pass initial states to the state.
And now if I refresh close up my Deftones open it up again
this in my view ex load my state you can see that the default data in the U X store is now the token
and the user from local story.