Before saving the that's our deeds of each.
We have to make sure the data is in the right four months.
That's what we are going to be doing in this lesson in so off we are going to create a value database
for the inhere.
I'll have a register of Jess.
This is going to be a validation middleware that once before actually registering to the user for validation.
We are going to install a package called Yelp and you can use any validation package you like.
This just seems very easy to use for me for this.
We are going to import or as Yelp from Yelp then we are going to define a validation schema here.
So Constance registers schema is going to be equal to yup I'm expecting an object with a specific shape.
And in here we won the name to be your upstream and this string is required.
We once that email to be a string and these strings should be an email on the string should be required.
Finally we won the password to be a Yelp string with a minimum of six characters and should be required.
Now we need to export defaults on Express middleware
and this middle way is going to call the register scheme of validation to validate the data.
First we need to get the data so we'll get name email and password
some requests that buddy next will call the registrar schema value data so register schema the filing
dates will pass in the name the email and the password and then when it's successful we are going to
return next.
Next simply means everything was fine so move on to the controller and in a situation where it doesn't
work out the catch then we are going to return a response that statues of 422 for validation failed
and the Jason of error.
So here we would receive an email from Yelp and would return that in the response so we also want to
return this promise from them to it.
OK so how do we use this middleware.
We are going to come to our roots off and we are going to import the middle way.
So imports register stuff detail
from server snatch and validated us smash register and let's make sure in a bubble.
See we have this server.
A Yes we don't.
So let's audit server is going to be server and we can have one bit off or validates all so I value
details and this is going to point to server slash value details and in our we can juice this too funny
details before the registration.
Simply going to pass in the register every detail and that's it.
Now we need to see the specific kind of email we get from Yelp to be able to handle this on the front
end.
So in our front end we have an error.
Let's just restart ourselves so that it goes away.
Stop the show up and starting their game NPM one death and now if I refresh click on Join now
visit my network.
Type in some fake details Oh and at the moment our form is always going to require the detail.
So Foster to the backend validation which protects our API.
Let's go to the client's stall off action and we are not going to pass the data.
OK so this is just so we can test and see the validation from the server.
So we are not going to positive data.
What we are going to do is simply field a form
even though we know the data is not going to be sent to the server.
But this is just so we can positive first Faysal foundation that we can sign up and we can see a fortune.
So look at the data and the way it comes from.
Yup we have a message and we have a path so path is for password.
A message is the message for that validation.
So this is how we are going to handle this in the register detail.
We are going to have an object.
This is going to be the path and this is going to be ever the message so that we can have a specific
object containing the key value pairs of all of our errors.
So now now we first saw this little that can stop and I'm going to pass in Fig data again
so if I click on sign up we can see we have password.
The password is required.
So in case a user is trying to connect to our API without using the clan site then API validation is
on point.
So at the moment we are validating to see that all the data is provided correctly.
What about situations where the user already exists in the database and is still trying to register
on the dot coms.
To do that we are going to require I use our model.
So import use user F1 models use
next.
We are going to try to find the user.
But we are going to have about three different listed levels of the then.
This is getting messy.
So let's use I think a week for the best convenience.
So we're going to have a try
and register value is going to be called in try.
So our register of on dates and our response 42 is going to be called in the catch and I'll delete this
so try to validate on your day I was returned with this and now after trying to validate the normal
data from the request we are going to try to validate if the user exists so existing user is going to
be a call to wait.
Use our model not find where the email is this email and let's find one.
So this is going to try to find an existing user with that e-mail.
And if the user is existing we are going to throw a new Yelp the validation error with all the properties
that are required here.
So for the validation error for us it takes in a message and this message is this user already exists.
Second it takes in the detail we value data which is request up body.
And thirdly it takes in the name of the path.
And this is not supposed to be an object it's just down to the constructor of the value data.
And finally it takes in the name of the path and would see it as email because it's to use all with
this e-mail that already exists.
Now what we do is we try to validate the scheme.
Is there any I was going to return a 42.
Then we try to find an existing use of that even and if there is.
We thought a new Yelp validation error.
Let's try this first.
I'm going to register a valid account with my email
people and sign up punishing we have an email on.
That's because here we are defining error in the catch we are supposed to get.
Sorry about that so let's try this again.
You can sign up and we have a photo to the sensible entity.
We have the password is required which means our validation works correctly but we are going to be agreeing
to come to the actions and make sure we pass the data so that we can test the email unique validation
plus inmate data
and we have a 42.
And you see this user exists already because I already have an account and you can see it's in the right
format.
Now we need to catch these errors and send them on our form.
So in registered to you we are going to have a catch
and this is going to give us the error and the first thing we do when we have an error is to toggle
loading so that it stops really.
Then we are going to look through each of the animals we have so object the keys for error
response detail.
And for each of them I'll call them feud.
Then we are going to set it was I see this that I was at
for a feud and he's going to be error response.
The data for that feud and now if we try this out try to register a user.
We have a 42 on for sensible entity and let's check our view component states
if we see our errors we have this user already exist as one of the errors but the reason why it doesn't
show in the form is because the error is not in the right form.
Let's try to find out what the right format for an error is so it looks like it requires a field name
and then it requires a message.
So in a form that means you have a field which is the field and we are going to have Miss each which
is our response.
The data for that field.
Now let's try this out.
I'll pass in my email my name and my password and when I click on that we see this user already exists
and that's coming directly from our API.
OK so what exactly did we do with this piece of code object that case is going to give you an array
of other keys in an object.
So first we have error DOD response the data on this is equal to the object we receive from the API
in this form.
When we call object the keys on this object it gives us an array with all of the keys in this object.
And this in this case just in then for each of the elements in these three we are going to call this
the error was that at and we pass in an object.
The first is field and fuel in this case is going to be email
and the next is message on message.
In this case is how all that responds the data of that feud.
And in this case the key is email.
So the response the are of email is this message right.
Yeah.
And that's exactly how we set the was to the form and then automatically seems view Justice reactive
it displeased to ours.
All right.
That's validation.
Handling both the front and then back in in application.