Let's handle the logging process in this lesson first on the south side.
We are going to create the method that handles authentication for users.
This method is going to get the email and password for the user.
And it's going to try to authenticate this user by festival finding the user so constant user is a waste
user that find one by email
and if it finds the user then it is going to compare the passwords to keep our controllers cleaner.
We agreed to have a method in our model that helps us compare passwords.
So we're going to see users Kumar not methods that compare passwords and it's going to be a function
and this function is going to taking the plain password and it's simply going to return be equipped
not confessing of the plain password with this not password.
So it's comparing the plain password passed by the user with the user's hashed password.
So in the controller we can check if user then if user does compare passwords
on will pass in the plain password then we are going to return response that Jason will pass in the
user.
We also need a token for the user so we can create a token using the user generated token method and
pass in the token in the response.
Now if the user was not found or if the passwords did not match at the end of this method we are simply
going to return a response that statue's 400.
The Jason with e-mail that sees these credentials do not match our records.
So first we try to find a user if we find a user.
And if they use us passwords compare successfully.
Now we are going to generate a token and return to that user.
But if the users passwords feel or we don't find the user then we return of foreign threats such as
quote with this error now that our End Point is done.
We need to take care of the value data.
So we are going to create a new log in the chess validator import or as you up from you up and will
create a logging schema.
And this is going to be up that object of a specific shape on the e-mail is going to be a string that
is required and we can also make sure it's an email
and the password is a stream.
With a minimum of six characters that is required.
Now all we need to do is exports default a function that takes in request response next.
And in this function we can return logging schema dot validate
dot then would return next and catch
would return response that statues of 422 the Jason with the error on the path being the error that
message.
And we actually have to get the error from the catch block and this looks a little cranky.
So let's use prettier to format this so that you can see clearly and great.
So now let's look up what we have.
We return logging that funny date and then if it's successful we call next.
And then if there's an error we catch the error and then we call or return a 42 with error that path.
An error message.
So we have to go to our router which is our water and import this funny detail import log in volume
Ito
from validators slash logging and finally we are going to pass this as a middleware to the logging accounts.
And that seat for the server side of the logging process.
We are going to connect this to the client side logging process in the next lesson.
And if there are any problems with our backend we are going to fix it.
Then.