Let's create a logging form first in the client pages in the log in the view.
I'm just going to copy everything in the register.
So we do not waste so much time.
Then the chop I'll change the title it's logging and we don't need the name input.
All we need is the e-mail and the password.
So now if we vitiate application and visited the logging screen we already have our form.
Let's change the text.
Like the signing text will change it to signing and when the button is clicked we are going to call
a method called logging and the model is not going to have a name it's going to receive a post logging
action and the method is going to be called logging
and it's going to dispatch an action code post logging when it's successful it's going to do exactly
the same thing to logging the user.
And when it fails it does exactly the same thing to handle the errors.
But we need to define the post logging action so we're going to come to start off actions and export
a new constants post logging and we'll define the action.
This is simply going to make a post request to the author slash logging end point and you pass the data.
Now let's try this out.
Let's open up a developer tools so we can monitor what's happening will pass in my email and if I click
on signing we have an enforceable entity seen the password is a request for you.
Let's check out the head us and it looks like the email and password are correctly past to the server.
So why is it telling us the password is a required field.
Let's check our validator again.
So in our value dates are for logging
it looks like we didn't pass request that Buddy to our logging schema validates also it doesn't validate
the right data.
So let's try again to logging and if I click on logging it also has these credentials do not match our
records because my password is wrong and now if I pass in the correct password you can see that it returns
a successful 200 we'd use a token and a user password and if we check out our low cost of each it persists
that low cost of each.
And if we check out a view each store.
We also have that data.