There is some duplication we have in some of our pages for example in the logging page.
We have the toggle loading function and we have the data loading property just because we want the button
to have a loading stage in the register.
We have exactly the same thing but as the application grows and we have more and more forms we do not
want these to be duplicated.
So we are going to create a mixing with a mixing
we can compost this data in one place so export default and object
first would you find a data property and he's going to have a looting state of force.
And second would define a method property
and he's going to have toggle loading function saw pasted there.
Now we are going to come to our register did you delete this toggle loading function and also delete
our data.
Looting property and we're going to import this mixing
from clients make sense slash form and we are going to use it on these components.
So makes sense for mixing we are going to do exactly the same thing in the logging.
So I'll delete loading remove toggle loading and import the mixing
and use it.
Now that this is done let's go to our register form and see if it's true of some suspected or we have
some errors on I think that's because the name of this folder is supposed to be mixed since we named
that and if we check our allies again we are good to go.
So let's try to register pass in a name pass in an email
and a password.
If I click on sign up we still have the loading state successfully but our registration process does
not stop loading.
And I think I know why a couple of lessons back when we dealt with the validation we didn't call next.
When everything is fine.
So remember to return or call next when the validation succeeds.
So let's just try this one more time to make sure that the registration process is all right.
So we're passing the fake name on a password
and great.
We redirect that to the home page which means everything is OK.