Let us continue refactoring into registered here after the user successfully sign saying we set the
users data to low cloud storage.
We also commit the set off and we redirect the user to the home screen.
We can actually handle this in a mixing since it's exactly the same thing we do for the logging.
So what we agreed to do is we're going to create a new mixing called off to Jess and this is going to
export default an object.
We're going to have methods and the first method I want to have is a method called set off and this
is going to set the users data to low cost on each and also comments set off.
So I'll cut that out of this component and here I'll call set off
this is going to take in a payload and will positive payload to Jason with the string.
If I am also proceed to the commit method we also need to import set off in this mixing if we have to
use it so import set of from actions.
We probably also want to bring in the redirect so distilled water that push to the home screen.
Okay.
Now in the logging all we can do is remove this and remove all of the duplicate functionality so we
don't even need to do this or we need to do is call set off and pass in response that data.
And we do exactly the same thing in our register.
So in our register I'm going to delete this all of this and simply call set off response not data.
Now I'm going to make the auth mix in to be a global mixing because we are going to also have some computer
properties like these authenticator in this mix.
So I'm going to import this mixing
from clients make sense of and use it view that mixing
of mixing.
Now let's try to use our authentication piece again to see the still work fine.
I'll try to signing
and signing works perfectly is to be directed.
And we have reflected all that to the earth mixing.
What else can we have in this mixing.
We are going to have computer property on this.
Property is going to help us get the authenticated user.
So let's do this.
We have user.
And this is going to return this that store that states that are not user.
And this is only going to work if the user is authenticated.
Right.
So how can we use this computer property.
It's available everywhere in the application.
So let's come to the home and try to do this use our DOT name.
And if we receive the whole grade you can see men off and then backwards.
Because this is the name of the authenticated user.
That's really cool right.
So our mixing can be used by any component and this is really useful.
Why don't we have a mix in for checking if they use ice authenticated.
We can have an off computer property and this is going to return this dot store that states that off
that user and we wanted this to be a boolean.
So it checks if the user is available in the store.
And this is when you tell us if the user is authenticated or not.
So in I mean we can check if the user's authenticated before displaying these two.
So we can see if off and if we come back it doesn't seem like it's working correctly.
Let's have a look.
It should actually see the if not off because if the user is not authenticated then we want to see the
signing on logging button.
Great.
So you can see those buttons.
Gone away because at this moment to use eyes authenticate it.
But we can also toggle that use us authentication states by removing this from local storage.
Why don't we have a very cool method to do that in off makes in.
We can have a method called on set off and what this is going to do is look our storage dot remove item
called off and he's going to commit a mutation called on set off and this mutation is basically going
to clear the users data from the Rudolph store.
Then Walter that push to the home page.
So I'm also going to import on set off and I'm going to make sure I define that in my store actions.
So export Constance on set of course on set off.
Now we need to handle this mutation.
So we going to import on set off into the mutations file and define a mutation with that deadly we are
not going to require any payload but we are going to set of use that should be law and state that token
should be known.
So now we can call the onset of method from anywhere in application.
So if I come to the main or the view I can have a diff with a V else and I can have a span that sees
logout and if I refresh grade you can see my logout button there.
So let's give this a couple of classes.
So the class is going to be cursor points are the text is going to be brown but the hover text is going
to be brown darkest and a click is going to call on set off.
So if I refresh and if I click on that great you can see that we are no longer authenticated.
So now we have an error from the home that sees cannot before putting name of law.
That's because we are displaying the name of a user even though the user is not authenticated.
So you want to also make sure that in your home or wherever you're using the off users details you want
to check if the user is authenticated before doing that.
So this is all we can do.
We can have an etch one that sees movement off and this is going to be the if not off and then we can
have another etch one with the same classes that sees welcome use for that name.
So this is going to be the else.
So this is only displayed if the user is authenticated.
So if I refresh great we do not see that.
But if I sighting and click on signing we have.
Welcome back.
Coulda displayed but it looks like the novel bar wasn't reactive.
Let's check this out.
We have the main.
And it says V if not authenticated then display this and the else displayed the logout.
Great.
We can see welcome.
And the name of the authenticated user and enough but also automatically changed looks like everything
works as expected.