Let's set up the clan site form for requesting a password resets when they use obviously the logging
screen.
And they are trying to logging.
This should have a button that says forgot password.
And if they click on it then they're presented with the form to request for a password we said link
first in the pages for that we are going to create a new page called forgot password.
How do we get everything in the logging view and pasted there so we don't consume so much time.
This is going to be called forgotten password as the title is going to have only an e-mail feud and
this is going to see send password reset link
next.
It's also going to use the form mixing.
But this is going to receive an action called Post forgot password the model is only going to require
the email and on click of the button it's going to call a method called forgot password
next.
This method is going to be called forgot password is going to dispatch post forgot password action and
after the password has been sent.
This is not going to authenticate the user it's just going to push their use out to the home page.
And if there are any errors it's just going to said that I was on the phone just like we've been doing.
OK now we need to define this action so we'll go to our store actions and export constant post forgot
password.
Let's define the action
and it's going to make a post request to slash passwords.
Slash e-mail and we'll pass the data from the phone.
Now we have to go to the logging and include a button or a link to the forgot password beach.
So right before the signing button which will have a div with a margin up and down all five and it's
going to have a Waltzer link
that says forgot password.
I'll give this a class of no on the line of text Brown and text center and also this is going to go
to auth slash passwords slash e-mail.
Now we need to register the rout for the forgot password speech.
So in our Welch file which are the new out path is going to be of passwords email and we need to import
that component
and we'll pass it down to the component property.
OK so let's try this out.
We have an error that sees no matching and talk.
And I think that's because we didn't close the routing link here.
Great.
So now we have the forgot password link Perth for some reason it's not centralised with the text center.
Let's try this out in the def dos have text center we can centralize this with Flex box by giving these
a class of flex and justify sensor in the logging.
I'm going to remove the texts and to give this a margin way of eight for most species.
Give this a display of flex justify sensor on items sensor.
Great.
So now if I click on forgot password it takes me to the forgot password beach where I can type and request
for a password reset link so if I check my network and I make that request we obviously receive a 4
or 4 from the API telling us this world does not exist in the next lesson we are going to define this
well and take care of the server side of this functionality.