In this lesson we winter sets up the rules and controls for application and also sets up API version.
First how create a large folder and in.
I'm going to create a version one folder.
This is going to contain all version one world for application.
And here I'd have an author James file first or import water from Express I'll create a new voter called
Oswald's or
I'll export this while John
now in my Rhodes file.
I'm going to also have an index digest file.
This is also going to be a voter but this water is going to contain all the worlds of application and
it's going to bring together all the versions.
First I'll import water from Express next all imports of water from Version 1 I'll create a new water
called version 1 voucher
and fish and one water is going to use the off water
which means that all the world's in the water are going to be prefixed by API slash V1 and then in the
future when you have a version to agree to a broader vision to offer water and you're going to also
use it with Version 2 then you get to export all of these wells.
So let's export version 1 Walter
and then in index stuff just file we can import it
and use it with your express application.
For the author worlds we also want to prefix them with us to make sure they're distinct.
Now we need a new folder called control us and since we have API versioning in place we also want to
have Version 1 for the controllers which are going to contain all the controllers for version one of
the API now on half of the controller.
Largesse which is going to be the controller for all authentication and points.
Here we're going to have a couple of vaults for authentication.
Let's start with logging which is simply going to be a function that takes in requests and the response
it would handle the logging process on which on the response would have a register.
Which takes in requests on response.
And now we are gonna have a couple more but we are going to export default logging and register so this
controller defines all of the authorized and exports them in an object.
Now in that of wildfire we can import a controller
and from the controller we are going to get of controller.
Now we can register the wilds for logging in off of our char that post logging is going to be off control
of the logging and auth while to not post
register is going to be off controller the register.
And just like that we have API version and with our controllers we have authentication rules set up.
We have our controller sets all given to download working at the moment.
This is the basic setup we need to be able to build a scalable and extensively powerful API.