Let's handle the forgot password functionality on the server.
The first thing I'm going to create a new model.
This is going to be called password reset.
This model is going to contain the future we need for resetting the user's password.
First I'll import Mongoose next I'll create a password resets Kimo and this is going to be new Mongoose
starts chemo first would have an email field which is the e-mail of the user requesting a password reset
will have a token which is a rundown each regenerates a token that we would send into use us email to
verify that they are actually the ones trying to reset their passwords and we'd have a created ad to
know when this password we said was generated and so also make sure that it has a maximum expiry of
30 days for example.
Now I'm going to export default a new model which is called password reset and the schema is going to
be password reset schema.
Next would go through our wallets and our register a new vault.
It's a post and it's going to be passwords slash email and he's going to be from the off controller
dot forgot password method.
Let's go to our off controller and define this method.
So we'll define constants forgot password as a function receives requests on response.
I would also export this function.
Now how do we want this to work.
What happens is we will create a password reset documents into the database with this users email and
this use US secret token and then we agreed to send an email to this user continued that secret token
and when they click on the link they are taken to application and they will see the reset password form.
For that we agreed to go to the user wanted to find some new methods on the schema.
The first method is going to be forgot password and this is going to be an sync function.
The first thing this is going to do is generate a token
and we'll make this seventy two characters.
Next it's going to create a new password reset document.
So we need to import the password reset model
and to create a new one we're going to see how each password reset that creates the token is going to
be this token.
And the e-mail is going to be this that e-mail referring to the user's email and the creator that is
going to be new dates which is the data at this moment.
Finally we have to send an e-mail.
So I'm going to see a week's new mail and this is going to be called forgot password mail that to this
that e-mail and this name is the name of the recipient.
That subject and the subject is going to be password resets the data because we are going to be sending
data to the templates.
They're going to be sending a You are all to the template and we are also going to be sending a name.
So the name is going to be does not name under you are all is going to be config that you are slash
off passwords reset slash then the token which is what we use to create the password reset tool.
And finally we just need to call a descent method.
But don't forget we haven't generated the forgot password e-mail yet.
So let's create this.
We going to say MP X friendly mail generates.
And the name is going to be forgot password.
So each generates at the meal.
So if we check our mails for that we have forgot password.
Now let's fill the details.
We're going to have for ask Jamal.
Hello would have a strong that is please they use us name and remember the piece of data is user name
by the same name and then would break and then we're seeing click this link to reset your password and
then we'd have an etch ref that displays that you are older we passed into these templates and he would
sending here for the text we are not going to use any strongbox and we are not going to have an etiquette
we're just going to have the link.
OK so that said all we need to do is now call this method in our Controller.
So our off controller we are going to see constant e-mail is equal to request and body constant user
is equal to our each user not find one email and we're going to see how each user dot forgot password
and you're going to see a return response to Jason with a message that says password resets link sent.
OK.
So let's see this in action.
It looks like our server is question on I think let's check the error a syntax error because we are
using tweets in a loan a awaits function.
So make sure we make that a sync and our server is good to go refresh.
Great.
So now when you send a push request it spend in
great we have a successful redirect.
Let's check mail drop and check our inbox you can see password resets you can see dos on my details.
Can we have here.
But could I click this link to reset your password.
And if we copy the link to check it out you can see off passwords resets and we have a token right there
for password reset and if you check the text you can see that sex is just as we define it.
All right.
So we are successfully sending a password reset link to the user but there's a couple of validations
we have to take care of before actually sending any link to a user.
We'll do that in the next lesson.