Let's quit a valid detail for a forgot password request.
So in a validates us we going to have one card forgot password and this is really important first.
Just so I don't type out much code I'm going to duplicate what we have for the logging.
I'm going to call this forgot password schema and we don't need to really did the password.
We just need to email then we are going to have a function body for this one and we are actually going
to use a sink a which because we have a lot of checks to do so make this a sink function fast.
We want to have our tri catch.
And here we are going to wait.
Forgot password not validated.
I will pass in request the buddy and if there are any errors we are going to respond with a 42.
So here we've validated that the data is correct.
Next thing is we have to make sure that a user exists with this email.
So which input they use our model
then I'm gonna say constants user is how we each user that find one
with email us requests that muddy that email and we're going to say if not user then throw a new Yelp
dud validation error.
And here first real positive message being this user does not exist.
Secondly the data will be validated which is requested buddy.
And finally the name of the feud which is email.
And next we are going to make sure we call next and what we can do is we can see request the user is
equal to the found user so that we don't have to find this user again in our Controller.
And we are going to go to our worlds file and we are going to import this value detail
and would use it on this world.
Which means after these validating ones if it ever gets to the controller we are already going to have
the author user.
So we just need to request that user or we can even get rid of this line on this one and do our wage
request.
The user forgot password as easy as that and it's going to send a password we said linked to off useful.
Now let's try this out.
Make sure it actually works.
So we'll try to sign in but we forgot our password so we'll pass in our email.
Click on send password reset link and great.
It works if we check out mail drop.
We have a link right there.
One final check.
We have to do is to make sure that this user has not already received a password reset link because
we can send many links to the user.
It's a little insecure because those are mainly tokens that can be used to assess our system.
So in our value detail we are also going to import the password reset model also after finding the user.
We are also going to check constant existing resets is going to be equal to our weight password reset.
Find one where the email is the email of the authenticated user and we probably should destruct other
email at the top so we can use it many times.
So email is going to be a culture request not buddy.
So we tried to find a password reset for this user even though use exists and if existing resets which
means there's already a password reset for this user we are going to throw a New York validation error
but the message would be different.
The message is going to see password resets.
Link already sends
then we still said they use our request and return next.
So now I already have a password reset.
Let's try to request another one
I'll forget my password.
But could a tumor that come when I click on this.
We have password resettling already sense because I've already received a link and that's some good
validation we have right there.
All right so the validation for the forgot good password is complete.
Let's move on to resetting the password in the next lesson.