Let's set up the reset password beach first.
We'll create a component
next.
With registered around on this path all this wealth has to match exactly what we sent in the email so
we can visit the e-mail and see the path so the path is off.
Passwords reset.
So we want to maintain that and the component is reset password
and make sure the component is important.
This component is going to be almost like the log in so copy everything from the logging on paste in
The Reset.
So this is going to see reset your password.
This form is only going to need an input field for password.
So this is going to be password and this is going to say until your new password and we are not going
to need a forgot password link.
And this is going to see resets password and our click is going to call a method called reset password.
It's also going to use the form mix in it's only going to need the password field the method is going
to be called reset password.
And the action is going to be post reset password.
Then when we are making the EPA request to reset the password we are not only going to send this dog
model we are going to send this to the model and we have to send the token that is in the power meter
so you can see off passwords reset and then we have a token.
So this took in this part of the world.
So we have to define this as a dynamic well with the idea dynamic field here or we can call these tokens
since that's what it is then in the reset password when we are making the API request we can add the
token in the body of the request.
And that's what is going to be this note about the programs that token then when we receive a successful
response we are going to stop looting.
We are not going to set off but we would redirect the user.
So this data out the push to the home page then if there are any errors will do exactly the same error
handling.
OK so let's see that in action.
If I refresh your speech.
Great.
That's our reset password form.
We can pass in our new password and then click on reset at the moment.
If we click on resets we're going to have some errors because we have anything else defined our action.
So let's define the action we come to store actions.
We're going to export.
Constant reset password.
And this is going to be an action receives context on data and simply returns clan the post to the end
point for resetting password asked passwords resets and it passes the data from the form and these data
also contains the token from the euro.
So let's try this again.
Plus password and it looks like we have another error or data is not defined.
Let's check this out.
And that's because I have a typo here.
Sorry about that.
Let's try this one more time and great.
We have 0 4 0 4 and not fun for my server because we haven't yet defined this end point in the next
lesson.
We are going to handle resetting the user's password on the server.