The first step in the reset password process is the validation.
So we are going to create a new value data called reset password largesse.
I'm going to copy everything and forgot password.
Because we're going to be using some of it first.
This is going to be reset password schema and we are going to actually expect the new password from
the user.
So we'd make sure it's a string with a minimum of six characters on each required.
Then I'm going to wait to reset password schema to make sure it's valid analogy structure out the passport
and the token from the body.
So once we confirm that the user's password is in the request body and it's a minimum of six card us
then we'll proceed to try to find the password reset for this user using the token.
So we are going to say constants existing reset is a weight password that find one and will pass in
the token.
So we are trying to find a password reset whether token is a token we received from the request and
we are going to check if the password we said does not exist then we are going to see invalid reset
Jochen and this is going to go to the password field.
Then if we actually get an existing reset we are going to try to find a user.
So I await user that find one where the email is the existing reset the email and this is how we would
get the authenticated user and then request on user is going to be user.
And then if there are any errors we will return the error that path.
And in this case it's going to be password.
And the message out on message now that we have validated so let's move on to registering to vouch for
the password reset.
So we are going to have off Walter that post passwords reset and we are going to use off controller
the reset password as the controller and we can import our newly created value data reset password very
detail
and use it as a meta where before our consulates code.
Now we'd head over to our controller and make sure we define the reset password method.
We'll make this a sync and I'll pass in reset password.
And how are we going to reset the user's password.
First we are going to find an update the user so I read user that find one and update web.
I would use that email to find a user.
So request that Buddy the user that email is which give us the e-mail of the authenticated user.
So what we want to do is probably get the user from the request OK so that we can just do user the email
and then we need to pass in the fields that we want to update.
And in this case we are going to be updating the password field and this is going to be request that
buddy not password.
But remember that we have to hash the password before saving of detail into the details.
So I'm going to import b create
and we are going to use it to hash the password.
So instead of passing or updating the plain password we are going to assign this to be create that hash
sync and we'll pass in requested buddy that password after updating the user's password.
We need to delete the password reset.
So we are going to see a wait password reset not find one and delete and to find it.
We are going to use that email.
So this is going to be user.
That email then we are finally going to return a response.
The Jason with a message that says password reset successfully.
OK.
So first we update the user's account then we delete the password reset that they use our used so that
the user can for that reset their passwords in future.
And then we reach an adjacent confirmation and also we have to use the password reset model.
So let's try this out.
We are going to type in my new password and click on reset password and we are redirected to the home
page.
Check out the response is a password reset successfully.
Everything works as expected to make sure the password reset was deleted.
We can try to request another password.
We said with my email and we can see that it actually sent the link because the password reset for me
was already deleted.