To have added security on resetting passwords when a user tries to reset their password we are going
to make sure that the password link has not expired.
So what we are going to do is make sure that the password link is no older than five minutes.
And how do we do that.
We are going to calculate the time in minutes.
And first we will get today's dates that get time minus a new dates from the existing reset.
That created at the get time and this is going to give us the time in milliseconds.
And we are going to divide this time in milliseconds by 60 thousand to get the time in minutes.
Then we are going to get the full number.
So Mark dot seal is going to rounded up to the nearest whole number and give us the time in minutes.
So we agreed to check if time in minutes is greater than five which means greater than five minutes.
Then we are going to for a New York validation exception.
So when you Yup I was seeing reset token expire.
OK.
And before actually doing this ever we are going to delete the password reset.
So we are going to see a weak password reset not find one and delete.
And we are going to use the token to delete it.
So we'll find a password we said with this token and delete it then we are going to throw this exception
that says request token or reset token expire to test this out.
I sent myself a password we said link about five minutes ago before starting to record the tutorial.
So I'm going to click on this link and try to reset my password if everything works fine.
Then this password link must have expired by now and we can see resets you can expire.
And if I try to click again we have invalid reset token because the password reset token has already
been deleted.
So I'm going to try to reset my password but this time I'll use a link that has not expired so I'll
send a password resettling and then I'm going to click on that link.
And try to reset my password and great.
It works now syncs the link has not expired.
All right.
That's some really good added security for resetting users passwords.
See you in the next lesson.