When users are registered they are sent an email to confirm the accounts.
Let's implement the functionality for compelling accounts.
First we are going to have an end point to that request of any detail.
So this is going to be email confirmed.
Jess in order to save us some time I'll copy everything in the log in and paste here.
This is going to be email confirmed schema and to confirm an email.
All we need is the token that was sent to the user in the email.
Then we agree to have a full function and the try catch first what value did that schema.
By seeing how each email confirms came out that validates plus a request not muddy.
And if this fails we are going to return a response that statues of faltering to the Jason and the error.
The type is going to be the key an error that message is going to be the value next.
Once we confirm that the token is in the request the next thing is to confirm if that token is valued.
For that we are going to import I use our model and then we are going to try to find a user who owns
that took.
We used to find one method and we'll try and use software to IMO confirm.
Code is this token if that Utzon was not found.
We thought a new validation error.
And first we have to pass the message.
Then the data that was value data and finally the key which is going to be taken.
But if the user was found which sets request the user to be equal to the user we found kind of authenticating
the user and then would return next.
So that's very detail.
First we finally did that the token was valid or provided in the body.
Then we find a user with dots who can leave the user was not found.
We thought a validation exception if the user was following.
Then we set the user to request a user and we call next.
Now we need to set up the rules for these endpoints.
So we are going to create a new out of Walter that post and this is going to be slash emails slash confirm
and we are going to use the off controller.
Don't confront evil method.
We also need to import the newly created value detail.
Then we'll positively detail as a meta way in off controller.
We have to define this method request and response and we are going to make sure that we exploit this
method.
Now how do we control a user's email.
We are going to find that user and updates.
So we use for that.
Find one and of deeds.
And then when you find a user using get email.
So remember we have to authenticate that user on the request object.
So we are going to see.
E-mail is request the user that email and we are going to be updating the email confirmed code we'll
set it to law and we'll also update email confirmed at and we'll set each a new date which is today's
date and we are also going to pass a third argument which is an option called new true so that once
this is done it's going to return to the updated version of the user then we are going to generate a
token for that user because the users data or profile has no data.
We need to update the clan site so that it cannot did the cached version of the user's data.
So this is going to be used for the Generate token and we are going to return response but Jason with
user and token and that's our confirm email functionality to be able to test this.
We need two sets of the client side votes on page to handle the incoming requests from wherever the
user clicks on the link and then make the post request we do this.
The next lesson.