To be able to confront the user's email on the clan site we would expose a route that the user visits
when they click on the activation link.
We will get the two can make a POST request to the server attempts to confirm the User's Accounts and
if everything is successful the user's account will be confirmed.
So the first thing we're going to do is create a beach called email confirm this speech is not going
to have much of a template.
It's going to have an edge 1 the text center dot NY 16 and it's simply going to say confirming in the
final script on exports default and object when this component is mounted.
For now we are just going to console that law.
This that our arms.
Now we need to register a vote for this page on this world has to be exactly what we sent to the user
window we're trying to activate the account.
So this is post safe.
And this is.
And this is the email we send to the user.
And this is the year oh so off slash emails slash confirm.
And then the email confirmed code.
So in our three vaults file the path is going to be off slash emails slash confirm and then would have
dynamic took in and the components is going to be email confirm that's in Port email confirm.
Now let's try to activate a user's account and see if the speech mounts correctly.
I want to clean up my database so we start afresh.
So I'm simply going to change my database environment vehicle and remember mortgage is automatically
going to create this database if it doesn't exist.
So now I'll visit my application try to register
click on sign up or use all ready access.
That's because if I change my involvement vehicle I have to stop the server and started to get.
Don't forget that.
Now let's try to register again on this demo.
We see a confirmation message.
Now let's see M. trop check my inbox and you can see the confirmation link.
So if I visit this link you can see we have the text that sees confirming email.
We probably want to design that better.
So the text should be brown.
Great.
That looks better.
Now what happens when this component is mounts that we are going to get this token.
So remember we locked the poems.
So if we check out the console we should see the bombs.
So we have the token that we are going to make a post request to the server with this token and attempts
to activate the user's account.
So to make that post request we are going to require an action.
Go to the store actions and we are going to spot a Constance call post confirm email and would find
a method.
This is going to make a post request to off slash emails slash confirm and it also received the data
not IMO confirm that you will import this action and when the component is small on set we are going
to dispatch it for the data.
We are simply going to have the token which is this.
Dots throughout the.
Token.
Now let's see what happens if we refreshed the speech and the component is mounted check out the network.
This also for true to say token is not defined.
That's what we receive from the server which means our media Web most likely has an error.
So that's it.
The email confirm and see what we have.
So we have chicken right here and took these nodes you find because we have to do structure so from
request the body if we have to use it.
If we try this again refresh the speech and after the pages refresh you can see confirm a movie tends
to us they use us fresh data.
Will confront Cody's know the email confirmed ad is the timestamp at this moment and we have a fresh
token for the user.
What we want to do is make sure this data is set for authentication so in the email confirm we are going
to have a dog.
Then we'll get the response I will call this not set off.
I will pass in response the data and if you don't remember if you check all the mix in the set of my
thought takes the payload sets its low cost on each commits each of the store and redirects to use that
to the homepage.
So for us to try out this to see if it works fine.
We need to activate a new account.
But before that let's see the case where there is a filter.
So if I refresh we have a filter to invalid confirmation code.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to add a dot catch and we are going to see this that router the push
to the homepage.
In future we are going to be able to flash messages so we are going to see to do flash a message to
the user but we don't yet have the flash functionality so we agreed to do that later.
So if we come on refresh or try to confirm the user's account of confirmed these are just related to
the homepage.
That's that's what happens when the user confirms their account.
Our logout and the register a new user
so we have welcome Emily Meyers.
So now if we check out our network or our application you can see that the user here is Emily Meyers
and the email confirmed could e in the user's data.
What we are going to do is we are going to click on confirm accounts and the use extradited to the homepage.
Now if we check the network again or the application and check out the user's data you see the email
confirmed code has been set too low and the email confirmed at it's a date.
OK.
So email activation works successfully.