Every good application should have such a confirmation box when the user has not confirmed your email.
Let's build our own so that the user can confirm your emails by clicking on this link.
So first we need to start this.
We are going to go to the main view and looking at this.
It's directly above the bar we have which is this and it looks like the text is centralized.
It has a whiff of fool.
It spans the whole container and has a little height on the text essentially aligned vertically and
horizontally.
So let's try that before this would have a diff with a full with a height of about 12 the text is going
to be brown.
The background is going to be good light test and the display is going to be flex.
The items are going to be sense centered
fiscally and justify center.
Now would you place in our text
please confirm your account.
And it looks like we're getting there.
The last thing we need is a link so the user can click on.
Let's look at the design.
It looks like it's just a text with an on the line so we probably can fix that.
Let's try this first.
I just wanted to type out all of the text and this part which is supposed to be on the line.
I'm going to give it the spawn and I'll give it a class on border and murder but on Brown and if we
look at that it's not the best.
Probably want to give this mother too and maybe Mother button too so that the motor I is only on the
bottom and maybe give this a margin left of two now that color is not very visible.
Let's try the brown darkest student and change and I think that's because we are defining bottom on
the color.
That's not needed.
So let's try with Von great so we have please confirm your email address and receive an email.
Click here to send email.
Now that we have the design let's give this across all pointer so that each more user friendly friendly.
Now if I hover right I have a pointer.
You can go ahead and give it some more styling.
Like on hole var the text should be brown dark est and when we hope VI you can see the text changing
on clique of this.
So I'm going to give a click what we want is to re send e-mail confirm we can define this method in
this mean or the view.
But I like to keep it clean.
I'll go to the off mixing and also define a new method they're called Reset IMO confirm for this we
are going to require a new action so I'm going to define an action called post re send email confirm
good to the actions and define it there.
First we have to export it
and next we have to define the matching action
or receive context and data.
So this is going to be client post to the off emails we send.
I will pass the data.
OK.
At the moment we are just passing data but as we did this summer side you're going to see we don't actually
require this.
First let's go to the mixing and make sure we dispatch this.
So this that stall the dispatch post we sent send email confirm an NDA.
Then we can redirect the user to the homepage and when there's an error they're still going to be X
to use.
That's the homepage.
The reason why we have a dot then until catches because we are going to be flushing different messages
and we want to put them in separate blocks.
OK so this is the setup for sending the e-mail confirmed for this user in the next lesson.
We are going to set up the server side to receive this request.