We agreed to handle the server side for rescinding a confirmed email to the user first only on authenticate
a user can ask for confirmation.
We sent because that's the only way we can know if the user is not confirmed.
So the first thing we are going to do is create a middleware to check if the user is authenticated in
a request.
I'm going to call these Me The Way of the Jess.
They're going to import JWT from Jason web token.
They're going to import the user for models and we are going to export default and a sync function would
have a try catch
on if there's any error at all.
We are going to return response dot statues of 400.
Jason with a message of on authenticated.
Now what are we going to do to verify they use us authentication stutters.
First we are going to get the token from the request.
We are going to check in to head us so request that headers dot assess token.
So if they use up is authenticated us SS token is going to be available in the header.
So first we're going to try to verify this token.
So we are going to see constant data is going to be closer JWT to verify and we'll pass in the token
and we also have to pass in the secrets that we used to sign all our tokens.
So I'm going to import
so would pass in config dot JWT and if JWT don't verify feels it was an error on the user receives on
authenticated.
Now we have to verify that the data in the jade Jason web token is coming from our server and to do
that.
We'll try to find a user so we user that find one or we can actually use defined by a method.
And this is going to be data dot IP because remember if we check how they use our model when we are
signing or token in the generic token method we put the idea in the payload.
So if the token is being sent back to us we expect the IDF in the payload to be the idea of the user.
Then if we successfully find a user request a user is going to be quote a user and we return next and
if we can't find a user.
So if not user then we are going to throw a new error and any other way through is going to be caught
by the catch block and it's going to reach us on authenticate it.
Okay so that's our off me to where now we need to go to our Wildstar and sets up rules for re sending
a confirmation email.
So while to that post slash emails slash re send and we will need to use our off me.
So I'll require it here
middleware slash off but I don't think we have the middleware in the ESA yet.
So let's check our bubble.
I'll see.
We don't.
So let's add that Middleware is going to point to server slash middleware.
Now we can use that to me the way here to protect that wallet.
And also we can use off controller Dauth we send confirm email.
So let's go to our controller and we send a confirmed email Constance recent call from email is going
to be a function and we'll make sure we export that function the first thing we are going to do is check
if requests don't use all that e-mail confirmed at all we can do if not requested I'll use that email
confirm that then we are going to confirm the user then if they use us email is already confirmed.
We are just going to return a graceful response response to Jason with a message.
Email confirm sent
just that.
So if they use us e-mail has not been confirmed.
We are going to send a confirmation but if it's us always being concerned we are just going to return
a 200.
OK so how do we confirm the user's e-mail.
I'm going to have a method request on user dot send e-mail confirmation and I'm going to have these
on the user.
So I'm always good to use our model to find a new method.
Came out that methods that send e-mail confirmation is going to be a function and dysfunction sends
the e-mail confirmation to the user.
But we already have a piece of code that sends the e-mail confirm this is it so post safe it sends this
e-mail.
What we are going to do is we are going to call these method in the send e-mail confirmation method.
So this is where we actually send the e-mail and then post safe.
We are going to call our wheat desk that sent send e-mail confirmation.
So after the use I received to the database this not sent e-mail confirmation is called and this method
sends an e-mail to confirm accounts to the user.
I can see we have everything we need this done e-mail this name does not name distant e-mail confirm
code.
OK.
So in our controller we just call that method.
It sends a confirmation email to the user just like it did when the user was registering.
Now we need to try all of this out so we'll counsel our clients.
This user is registered.
We are going to click on we sent
Oh I think I have to stop my server or stop my server and start it.
And it looks like we have an error.
We have a wait and re son confirm e-mail and that's because this has to be a sync function.
OK.
Sorry about that.
So very starts in and we're good to go.
Now let's refresh they use ice not confirmed if I click on to be sent.
We have a bad request because the user is not authenticated.
Now we need to put the authenticated users token in the request had us so that the user can be authenticated
so forced to do that.
We are going to have to set up exhibits to automatically add the token would do that in the very next
lesson.