When trying to send a confirmation email we have a 400 but requests because they use ice not authenticate
it for us to authenticate all requests for the user.
We are going to have an egg use intercept.
Let's go to our issues exudes largesse and we are not going to export to an instance.
We are going to save the instance as is yours and we're going to export it.
Then we're going to have excuse that intercept US DoD request.
So we are intercepting all requests that use and will pass in a function that is going to be called
every time we make a request.
Here we are when you receive the agents config and we can modify these config and return a new version.
First we want to make sure we always return the config.
Secondly we want to know if the user is authenticate.
If they use sites authenticated we will get the to conform the view store and Apache to this request
as the header that our server is expecting first to get the store they're going to import stuff from
store and to check if the user's authenticated with which you see store that off the user and have a
streak boolean and to enforce the check.
We can also see and store that off the token.
Then we are going to set config that had us to be equal to assess on the score.
Chicken we are going to set the authenticates and use us token.
So this is going to be store that state.
And this is actually supposed to be states right because we want to get the state of the store so startled
state not off.
So when you say store that state that off that took it and if the user is not authenticated it's not
going to modify the head us just going to return it.
So that's it.
Now let's try to confirm the user's email again.
If I click on this reset to have a bad request so let's check to see if that took in was sent so you
can see the assets token was added to the request by agents.
Now let's verify exactly why we still have one authenticated.
We are going to go to mid away and to debug this in the catch.
We are going to console that love the error
open up launch serve our warning make the site request again.
And now we have the 400.
If we check our API to see the error we have secret a public key must be provided and that's coming
from Jason Webb.
Which means there's something wrong with a public key so let's check out the middleware and see what
we were passing in.
So we are passing in config to JWT.
Now let's check our config and we actually called JWT secret and get a blue cheese on undefined.
That's why Jason Webb token is telling us we must provide the secret key.
OK so let's let our server refresh and now if we make the request again we have e-mail confirmed sense
coming from our server but that was really fast and I think that's because this user is already confirmed.
Let's see if this use ice confirmed in the view store.
Check out the user's data the user has only been confirmed.
So let's try this with a user that has not been confirmed.
So I'm going to register with a new user
sign up this user successfully locked in with this user.
But we've not confirmed this User's Accounts.
If we take a little trap that's they use us accounts Nick.
Now let's click on recent e-mail.
You can see it takes a while.
It's spending and now we have a successful response.
And if we check out again you can see a new e-mail confirmation link has been sent to this user.
OK finally let's confront the User's Accounts and now the user's account is confirmed.
Let's check out the unique start to see the user's data.
If we load our stage you can see that e-mail confirm it is not.
Which means this user has been confirmed but we still see this bar.
So we need to restrict when this bar is showing.
If we look up we can see through the bar.
So this bar will only be there if the user is locked in and the user has not confirmed yet e-mail.
So the first thing we're going to do is we're going to go to mix in for off and find a new computer
property called confirmed and this is going to return this that store that stage that cost the user
the e-mail confirmed at.
And we can cast it to a fossil bullion.
So confirmed if this value is true then it's going to give us true.
But if these values undefined and you give us false OK.
So now in pages mean the view file we can have a V on this element so we can have the F off which means
only show up if the user is authenticated.
And now the user it's not authenticated.
So we can't see it.
Next we would log in
and now the user is locked in and we can still see the bar but this user is authenticated and verified.
What we're going to do is add another check and not confirmed.
So if you use eyes locked in and not confirmed then we will truly spot.
And now we can see that the bar is gone because this user is locked in and confirmed.
Now let's log out would sign up with a new user that is not confirmed sign up and now we can see the
bar why Deb because the user has not confirmed the account.
Now let's check a little drop click on this to confirm the user's account.
And as soon as they use ice confirmed the reduction of refreshes and you can see that the bar is gone.
This is really reactive.
And it's also.