If we check out our application we can see that importing files requires us to use the dot dots right
here.
This is not very clean and we are going to use a bubble blogging to help us import files cleanup to
install this would run npm install safe def bubble plug in modules over
once this is installed.
We need to configure it in our bubble.
Our CFO.
So we'll have plugins and inhere would have an array for mods to resolve.
Which takes in on objects.
Would define define the words which is the woods folder.
And finally would define aliases that are going to be used to our application.
The first I'm going to define is control us and this is going to go to server slash controllers and
what this means is every time we write controllers in an application bubble is going to know to look
into the server slash controllers folder.
Let's try with our off.
We can change this to controllers and try to start our application
we can see that it successfully starts because mobile is still able to load that file.
This is a much cleaner way of using or importing fast application.
Let's add one for the config.
And one for the mouse.
To differentiate the aliases that we have from the normal load modules we can have an odd symbol right
here.
Just to put a little difference between the two.
So here we can have a controllers in an index of the Jets.
We can replace these with droughts and this type config you can see that bubble steer successfully restarts
because it understands exactly how to produce farms as we built along the coast.
We agreed to add more resources as need be.