We are going to implement a complete flash messaging system.
So watch these guys.
This is going to be awesome.
The first thing we want to do is to be able to flash from anywhere in application.
Which means we're going to put this data in the view store so we are going to consume the clans store
folder and would have a new folder caught flash in here.
We'll have an index digest for the default state and we are going to have a mutations
Jess that exports an object.
We are also going to export some constants so export constant flash message and export constant.
Last message we are going to import our media mutations and will export default and objects which will
define states to be an object with messages are we will pass the mutations.
Now we need to register this flash module with our store.
So we are going to import flash
and pass it as a module.
OK.
So how do we flash messages and how do we clear them.
Let's have a global mixing called flash.
This is going to export defaults and objects with methods.
We're going to have a flash method the flash method will take in the message and the type by default.
The type is going to be success.
Then let's import all our mutations for flushing.
So import form stores slash flash mutations.
The first one is flash message and the second is clear flash.
Message
what we want to do is this the store that commit flash each and we are going to pass a payload.
This is going to contain the type of flash message and the message itself.
Then after three thousand milliseconds or after three seconds we want to clear out the flash message
that we just flashed.
But we need a way to be able to identify the exact flash message that we want to play so that if there
are three different flash messages we would only cloud a specific one that we want to do that.
We are going to install a package called you you I.D. to help us generate unique I.D. for all flash
messages.
We would import you I.T. package and we are only going to be needing version 4.
Don't worry about what it means.
It's just going to generate a random unique idea for us.
Now when a new flash is caught we are going to see constant I.D. you I.D. and we will pass the I.D.
to the comments then we are going to have a set timeout and we are going to commit Clef last message
and the payload for clever flash message is going to be the eye of the flash that we want to play and
the default is going to last for three thousand milliseconds which is three seconds.
So we flash so put the flash message to the store and declare flash to remove it after three seconds
of Flushing.
So we are going to go to the mutation and handle both cases when we flash a message.
We received the states on the message and we have which is a state the messages which is the messages
we is equal to state.
The message is with a new message and when we clear a flash we receive the states and the idea of the
flash.
And we are going to see state messages as equal to state the messages that feuds are and will filter
out the specific one with that idea.
So we are going to filter out all the messages where message and I.D. is not equal to Heidi and that's
it all we need to do now is implement these flash mixing with our application.
So we need to import the mixing import flash mixing and use the mixing
now that we use this mixing we can flash from anywhere in application.
Let's start by flushing the out.
So when the user logs out.
We want to flash to do that.
We are going to go to our off mixing to the onset of my thought and I'm going to call this the flash
successfully locked out and the default type is success.
OK now that we are flashing let's go to our browser log out and see if the actions are dispatched so
this in my view store and I'll click on logout and often logging out.
It looks like we receive an error that sees invalid attempts to spread known.
A terrible instance.
And I think I know where the problem is coming from.
We have a message instead of messages and when we try to spread messages it was an error because messages
is not defined.
So in our flash default we have to make sure this is messages.
OK.
So let's logging so let's logging
and let's log out and you can see flash message was committed and left last message was committed with
seconds later OK.
So that's our flashing system in the next lesson.
We are going to display the flash message depending on what the type is.