Let's display flash messages.
That's the final step in our client.
We are going to create a new flash component.
That view and we are going to mount this flash component in our means so that it's available on all
pages.
So in our mind a view I'll define the scripts
and I'm going to import flash from components I'll define it
as a component and I'll mounts it right at the top.
Now the flash component is going to have access to the view store but I'm going to have a helper in
my flash suggests which returns a computer at least of all messages from the view store.
So this is going to be called messages or let's call it flash messages.
So it's clear and this would return this not store that states not flash not messages which is under
way.
So in our flash crash we have to design this component and it's going to look pretty much like our e-mail
confirmation but with a few changes
the first change is the text in it the background is not going to be good light us the by going is going
to depend on what type it is the text is always going to be white and all of the detail is always going
to be centralized.
So first I'm going to have a DPH that wraps everything so that I can use a V4 on this element.
So V for message in flash messages will bind the key to be equal to message does I.D. since we know
it's very unique then we are going to display the message that message.
And we're also going to bind on classes for example.
Class is going to be quotes one object and the background is going to be green if the message that type
is equal to success.
And the background is going to be read Heath message not type is equal to error like that.
OK.
So our flash components mindset let's try to flash a message how signing we can actually just put this
flash right away for signing.
So we are going to go to the logging component.
And after a successful signing we're going to flash a message this flash signing successful.
Now let's try to sign in with an account
we can see a beautiful green message that says signing successful and after three seconds it's taken
the week.
Now there's a really strange bug in application.
Right now we are signed in but we can see signing on joined now here.
I'm going to look into this when we're done with the flush system.
But now if I refresh we have logout.
If I log out we have successfully locked out.
Now let's add this flash messaging on all of the actions we have.
So I'm going to go to the register each and after a successful registration I'm going to flash successfully
registered.
I'll also go to the e-mail confirm.
And if the user successfully confirms I'm going to flash a message does this e-mail confirmed.
But if there is an error I'm going to flash a message that says Error confirming e-mail and I'll make
sure that the type is error.
If we go to a forgot password we do exactly the same thing.
Who flush a message that sees password resets link sent it expires in five minutes.
This is very important so the user knows.
And then if there are any errors which display to us on the form.
OK so I think we've covered most of the actions.
Let's try to use some of those actions so we'll pass in a strange user sign up and we have successfully
registered and now we have a link that says Click to re send email.
We probably should also have a flash message for this.
So we agreed to come true our of mixing and this is the recent e-mail.
We're going to have this flash successfully.
We sent confirm e-mail.
And if there are any errors we're going to see this the flash our re sending confirm e-mail.
OK.
So let's try.
We click on we send e-mail and we have the message that they successfully re sent confirm e-mail.
But what I want is for the flash message to always be at the top.
So I'm going to move flash to the top OK so let's try sending the e-mail confirmation again and now
the message is at the top.
Now let's log out and try to signing or actually try to forget our password
and now we see the message that says it expires in five minutes and if we click on password reset click
on the link
reset password.
We don't have any message so let's go to reset password and flash a message.
This dot flash password has been reset.
OK.
So that's it for Flash.
Message in.