So always keep our quote cleanly formatted.
That's in store preshow npm install save.
Def creature
we can have a preacher our c file and this is going to contain all of the configurations that we want
for preacher.
Personally I like the top with of four also I can make sure that semicolon is set to false because I
prefer writing code without semicolons.
I can also set single quotes too true.
So that looks cleaner.
There's a ton of configurations that you can have for preacher.
This is the ones I like to work with in package the Jason.
We're going to add a new script that we can use to rapidly format our code.
This is going to be called preacher here.
We're going to have the preacher man dash dash right so that when preacher formats the code he's going
to see the changes and we are going to have all the flowers and in the Jeffs in the coin folder to be
formatted.
So let's try this one NPM one preacher and if we check out you can see that the config was formatted
for us you can also check out a controller.
It was automatically formatted as record.
We are always going to run creature to make sure that our code is cleanly formatted and presentable.