Not that we have the full structure of our server.
We have the controls on the.
We are going to start building or setting up our phones and with weapons.
So let's go ahead and install by
and ISO Version 4.
We need to also install wetbacks like
Next we'll create a Web site config file the first thing we're doing this far is require that EMV on
we'll call the config function.
This is so we can use environment variables in our power configuration.
For example when we want to know if the application is in production next number which import is the
path
our config is required to export an object and the default or the base configuration is an entry point.
And this is going to be client slash index digits which is going to be the base for off just application.
Then you're going to have an output the file name is going to be app.
Yes and the path is going to be path not resolve Durning server slash public.
That's go through these together.
What we want to do is we want to have a plan for the ship all of our clan code is going to leave it
which will have an index largesse which is the roots of our clients.
And when Web views our clan it's going to put the content or the output of the built into a public folder
in so rough order.
And once this is put here we are also going to build the server and have maybe a disk for that with
the final outputs of our project which is what we are going to run in production.
So let me show you how this is going to work.
I'll open my particular Jason which so have a script called Build clients.
This is going to one Web Park mode equals production.
Remember it's always possible mode configuration because it's required by wetback.
Let's also make sure I went back on forecast the mode option which I see a process that EMV not load
EMV or development
which means if the model is not defined in the node environment we should just use development by default.
So we have a script called build plan and this is going to run weapon.
So let's run this on see what we have as output NPM one viewed science
if we check the public folder you can see we have an update just magnified file bundled and put there
by wetback.
So when rep builds a clan it is it in the public folder.
Now how do we finally send this code to production.
We are going to have a view serve our scripts and this is going to run Babu on the server for the and
we configured the output directory to the disk and we'll copy all of the files that and not JavaScript
files.
So the way this looks is if we want NPM on build server it's going to build all of the javascript from
the server folder and place it in this list and you can see right now this uses yes 5 which is the best
2 1 in production and also it also copy the app which is our clients.
So we build a client and then we build our server.
So let's just have a built create which is going to do both NPM run
view clans and build server
configuration at the moment can build our clients and place it in the public folder of the server and
we also have a bubble script to build our server and place it in a dist folder.
We probably should at this to get it now in the next lesson we'll continue preparing our client site.