Let's install a web server so that we can serve our client side directly from our server side npm install
safe def where part def middleware
with this middleware we agreed to serve our client site and I'll show you exactly how our server indexed
suggests which import these middleware
and I'll also import Rep. Mark
and I'm also going to import the wetback config.
We'll create the compiler
and we do this by calling wetback with the wetback config.
Then we use the middleware to use my dad for me to where I will pass in the compiler.
And what happens is every time we launch our server the weapon gets me to where he's going to use the
configurations from wetback which is this compiler to launch our client site.
If we want NPM on Def
we haven't ever seen what package notifying.
That's because here with a capital letter and once it's compiler it you can see we have load money on
in here and we also have web compiling successfully which means I express over a serving with the clients
but for us to be able to actually view something in a browser.
We need to pass contributions to the Web by the way.
The first thing we need is actually an index that is gem of file.
This is going to serve as the template for our client site.
This is going to be called and easy in the title and here for now I'm just going to have an S-1 that
sees the MTV end project.
Next we're going to use the app there just create here in our index that is GMO so secret sauce is going
to be equal to the Jess so that every time weapon builds this Abdul Jess file it's going to dump the
contents in the after Jess and index that extra noise when you use the new version and finally in our
server every time the user makes a guess request to our application which is unknown to start I'm putting
this after I've registered all of my votes so this is a wild card.
Well what is going to happen is we're going to response that sent file past the resolve then the oblique
slash index that is Gemma lets you spot the top
and we are instructing Xpress to always respond with the public slash in next load estimate.
When the user makes a request to an unknown world and our client site is going to handle the client
side bouncing from its end so let's visit our application.
We have an error that sees response is not defined and that's because in this world we have to receive
requests and response objects Loman restarts web views.
If we refresh we have the MDA and projects.
Why.
Because Express has been instructed to respond with the index of extra Jomo Fry every time an unknown
world is assessed.
In this case the Homeworld is on.
If we view the beach source you can see we have the app just creeps right there which is the result
of wetback building the planned site assets.
So as we build along all of our client side assets are going to be in the apologist file and wetback
is going to continue putting the contents here and we agreed to view the changes in that bottom line.
Make sure you have this sets up now catch in in the next lesson.