Let's add by bootloader you know that on VHS to application for wetbacks to be able to compare download
view files.
We need to view loadout for Web site to be able to compare down yes six down to iOS 5 that the boss
understands we need to have.
So npm install
view louder and louder to configuration load us.
We are going to have our module key here would have rules and there's is going to be an array of all
US test is going to be a regular expression for fires and in the chest and in this case we would use
the bubble Ludo so for all fire spending we don't just use the bubble loadout and we'll have another
test and this is going to be for all fires and in our view in this case we are going to use
the view loader for The View low that's worked properly.
We also need to use the view Luda blogging.
So we are going to require this
registered to plug plugin.
Now if we run our application NPM on death web by comparison successfully but as a package we are missing
unfortunately able to detect that package.
I want to show how required it is we are going to add a dot view file to our product.
So I'm going to have a page's folder here on half of me the view in my index suggests I'm going to import
view from view.
Oh that's right.
We haven't installed you Sol stone view npm install safe you now create a new view instance.
We need to pass in the elements in this case up and we need to pass a render function what is going
to be when that when the few instances mount that we are going to render the main component.
So all important main form pages slash mean that you understand the function is going to taking that
creates an immense function called create elements on the meat or you're going to see really popular.
It's simply an etch like this.
This basically means render the main component.
So we have a indexed Digest which mounts are main component and we I mean the view from another which
sets a wetback.
It's supposed to compile down the main The View and The Indexed digest and put them in a public folder.
Jess.
Let's try this out.
NPM one def and we have an error and this is the reason why I let this happen because I want you to
be able to read through the errors and detect exactly what you do.
For example in this case I specifically left out the package called view template compiler which is
a peer dependency for the view Luda.
So after reading this I want understanding exactly why weapon is really.
I know I have to install the view template compiler not I have this installed everything should be fine.
So NPM on Def serve us at that successfully and wetbacks successfully compound in our main let's add
a template here.
I'll have an etch one that sees the main components and in our public indexed with Eskimo instead of
having this patch one we're going to have a diff with ideas of how and when this javascript is low that
is going to Molins or render the main component on the element with idea of just like we describe.
So now if we visit local voice for three thousand upvotes so you can see we have the main component
and just like that we are successfully loading view Jess from our server site.