Let's go CSX load us so that we can load CSX in our templates npm install CSX loader.
We're also going to be installing mini CSX extracts blogging which is going to help us separate CSX
from javascript Bondo using web Park.
Now I need you to know exactly why we are installing these plugins.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to try to use CSX without registering these plugins and went back
to see the results.
So here I am a star supporter and here I'm gonna have a mean that see assess now how art or style for
each one color is going to be red.
And in my index suggests I'm going to import
stars mean that CSX now would run our project and piano on Def
and we have an arrow and shows as we may need an appropriate low that's handled this file type and that's
exactly why we need a CSX loader so in each comes our way configuration and add a new load up to our
roofs.
Copy this one and here we're going to find all files that end with CSX and for those fires we would
use the CSX loader and after that you can see where compare successfully and if you sit up well so everything
works perfectly Max.
We need to be able to extract this CSX out of our javascript scripts and have it separately in a success
file.
So to do this we are going to use the many extra accesses blogging so constant many extra accesses blogging
sequels mini extracts.
Yes this book is now to use this blogging.
We are going to have multiple load us for CSX.
So instead of putting an object we're going to pass on our way.
And we agreed to pass in many extra blogging but loader as the first one and CSX loader as a second
one.
And the order is very important because whip out process a CSX loader before actually processing the
minute extra accesses blogging load up so that I can compress assets and then loaded with the extra
accesses blogging.
So now we also need to register this blogging.
So in our blogging section we'll have new media extracts RSS blogging and now we have we're part successfully
compiling the mini extracts RSS blogging we need to pass a contribution which is the finding that we
want to see ISIS in the project extract that too.
In this case Abdel see ISIS so if we want NPM long build client we can see the updates RSS file and
this contains the CSX form our project we want to also make sure that this ISIS fighter is linked in
our index stood Joan of Arc so we'd have a link and this is going to be the CSX and when we are in development
mode which is NPM on Def if we refresh our browser you can see that the CSX is not applied since we
are linking the update CSX is not indexed extra file now any for the changes that we make in the CSX
automatically reflect it.
So you can see weapon automatically compilers and then puts the content in the update SPSS so you can
see weapon automatically compilers and when we refresh our browser these changes are reflected.